like to point out that while I'll be presenting today is partly my work in
오늘 발표됩니다 동안 것은 부분적으로 내 일이라고 지적했습니다
collaboration with others and sometimes I'm presenting work done by people in my
사람들에 의해 수행 다른 사람과 때때로 내가 제시하고있어 업무와 공동으로 제
group that I wasn't really involved in but its joint work with many many people
정말 많은 많은 사람들이 있지만 공동 작업에 참여하지 않은 그룹
you'll see lots of names throughout the talks so take that with a grain of salt
그렇게 에누리이 걸릴 회담을 통해 이름을 많이 볼 수 있습니다
so what I'm gonna tell you about is kind of how Google got to where it is today
오늘날 어디에 구글이 있었는지의 종류에 대해 그래서 나는거야 무엇을 말해
in terms of using departing in a lot of different places the project that
다른 장소 프로젝트의 많이 벗어나지 사용의 관점에서 그
involved in actually started in 2011 when entering with spending one day a
지출 일일 A를 입력 할 때 실제로 2011 년에 시작에 관여
week in Google and I happen to bump into him in the micro kitchen and and I said
구글의 주와 나는 마이크로 부엌에서 그를 우연히 일이하고 나는 말했다
oh what you were doing was like I don't know but I haven't figured out yet but
나도 몰라처럼 오 무슨 일을 하였다는했지만, 난 아직하지만 파악하지 않은
ignore laps or are interesting and I got the call and turns out I don't
바퀴를 무시하거나 흥미와 나는 전화를 받았는데 내가 안 밝혀
understand pieces on parallel training of termites like ages ago I don't want
전 원하지 않는 나이와 같은 흰개미의 병렬 교육에 조각을 이해
to tell you how long ago
당신에게 시간을 전합니다
back kind of in the first exciting period relax and I always kind of really
다시 최초의 흥미 진진한 기간에서 휴식을 취 항상 종류의 정말
like the computational model they provided but at that time there was a
계산 모델처럼 그들은 제공하지만 그 시간에이 있었다
little too early like we didn't have a big enough data set for the number of
우리의 수를 충분히 큰 데이터 세트를 가지고 있지 않은 것처럼 너무 일찍 조금
computation to really make them sing and Andrew kind of sad 0 will be interesting
계산은 정말 그 노래와 앤드류 슬픈 0의 종류 흥미로운 일이 될 것이다 만들려면
to train but now I'm like ok that's on the phone so we kind of collaboratively
훈련하지만 지금은 우리 종류의 공동 전화의 확인과 같은거야하기
started the brain project to push the size and scale of normativity training
규범 교육의 크기와 규모를 밀어 뇌 프로젝트를 시작
and in particular we were really interested in using big data sets in
특히 우리는 큰 데이터 세트를 사용하여 정말 관심
large amounts competition to tackle perception problems in my marriage
많은 양의 결혼 생활에 대한 인식의 문제를 해결하기위한 경쟁
problems and read them I often found Coursera and kind of just away from
문제와 나는 종종 코 세라를 발견하고 종류의 단지 거리에서 읽을
google but since then we've been doing a lot of interesting work in both kind of
구글하지만 그 이후로 우리는 두 종류의 재미있는 작업을 많이 해왔습니다
research areas in a lot of different domains you know one of the nice things
다른 도메인의 많은 연구 분야는 좋은 것들 중 하나 알고
about no matter their incredibly applicable to many many different kinds
많은 많은 다른 종류의 약에 상관없이 자신의 믿을 수 없을만큼 적용 할 수 없습니다
of problems as I'm sure you seen in this class and we've also deployed production
나는 확신 같은 문제는이 클래스에서 본 우리는 또한 생산을 배치 한
systems using our mats in pretty wide variety of different products all kind
다른 제품의 모든 종류의 매우 다양한 우리의 매트를 사용하는 시스템
of give you a sampling of some of the research some of the production aspects
의 당신에게 생산 측면의 일부를 연구 몇 가지의 샘플링을 제공
some of the systems that we've built underneath the covers including kind of
우리의 종류를 포함하여 커버 아래에 내장 한 시스템의 일부
some of the implementation stuff that we do intend to follow to make these kinds
우리가하려는 않는 구현 물건 중 일부는 이러한 종류를 확인하기 위해 수행하는
of models run fast and I'll focus on her mouth but a lot of the techniques are
모델의 빠른 실행하고 나는 그녀의 입에 초점을 맞출 것입니다하지만 기술이 많이 있습니다
more
더
a couple that just months before you can train lots of different kinds of
당신이 전에 몇 달은 다른 종류의 많은 훈련을 할 수있는 몇
reinforcement algorithms or other kinds of other kinds of machinery industrial
강화 알고리즘 또는 기계 산업의 다른 종류의 다른 종류
thats ok Kevin hear me actually some of the back if it comes up the time I one
그것은 시간을 제공하는 경우 확인 케빈 실제로 뒷면의 일부를 내 말 듣고 그게 전부 내가 하나
of the things I really like about the team we've put together is that we have
정말 우리가 함께 넣어 한 팀에 대해 좋아하는 것들을 우리가 가지고있다
a really broad mix of different kinds of expertise so we have people are really
사람들이 정말 그래서 우리가 가지고있는 전문 지식을 다른 종류의 정말 다양한 믹스
experts at machine learning research you know people like jeffrey hinton other
기계 학습 연구에서 전문가들은 제프리 힌튼 다른에게 같은 사람을 알고
people all that we have large-scale distributed systems builders I kind of
우리는 대규모는 시스템 빌더를 배포 한 사람들은 모두 내가 가지
consider myself in that more in that mold and then we have people can do with
그 금형이 더 자신을 생각하고 우리가 함께 할 수있는 사람이
a mix of those skills and often some of the projects we work on you collectively
우리가 집단적으로 당신 작업 프로젝트의 일부 종종 그 기술과의 혼합
put together people with these different kinds of expertise and collectively you
집합이 다른 전문 지식의 종류 당신과 함께 사람을 넣어
do something that none of you could do individually because often you need both
자주 모두 필요하기 때문에 아무도 개별적으로 할 수 없었다 뭔가를
kind of large-scale systems thinking and machine learning ideas so that's always
즉 항상 그래서 대규모 시스템 사고의 종류, 기계 아이디어를 학습
fun and you often kind of pick up and learn new things from other people
재미와 당신은 종종 종류의 픽업과 다른 사람들로부터 새로운 것을 배우고
script outline actually this is from hold back so you know you can kind of
당신이 할 수있는 종류의 알 수 있도록 스크립트 개요 사실이 다시 보류에서입니다
see the progress of how Google has been applying deep learning across lots of
어떻게 구글의 많은 걸쳐 깊은 학습을 적용되었습니다의 진행 상황을 볼
different areas with this is sort of when we started the project and we
우리는 프로젝트를 시작하고 때와 다른 지역 일종의이다 우리
started collaborating with a speech team a bit and started doing it with some
음성 팀 비트와 함께 공동 작업을 시작하고 시작 일부 그 일을
kind of early computer vision kinds of problems and as we had success in some
문제의 초기 컴퓨터 비전 종류의와 같은 종류의 우리는 몇 가지에 성공했다
of the other teams that Google would say hey I have a problem too and like they
다른 팀의 구글은 헤이 나도 그들과 같은 문제가 말하는 것
would come to us or we would go to them and say hey we think this could help
우리에게 올 것 또는 우리가 도울 수 있다고 생각 헤이 우리는 그들에게 가서 말을
with your particular problem and over time we've kind of gradually not so
특정 문제와 시간에 우리했습니다 종류의 점진적 그리
gradually expanded the set of teams on areas that we've been applying these
점차적으로 우리가이 적용되어 한 분야에 팀의 세트를 확장
kinds of problems and you see the breadth
문제의 종류 당신은 폭을 참조
different kinds of areas it's not like it's only computer vision problems so
그것을 같지 지역의 다른 종류 그렇게 만 컴퓨터 비전 문제입니다
that's that's kinda nice we're continuing to grow which is good and
즉 그것이 우리가 선한 성장을 계속하고 좀 좋네요 그리고
part of the reason for that broad spectrum of things is that you can
사물의 광범위한 스펙트럼에 대한 이유의 일부는 당신이 할 수있는 것입니다
really think of that as these nice really universal system that you can put
정말 당신이 넣을 수 있습니다이 좋은 정말 보편적 인 시스템으로 그 생각
lots of different kinds of inputs into you lots get lots of different kinds of
만약에 많은 입력의 다른 종류의 많은 다른 종류를 많이 얻을
outputs
출력
out of them with you know slight differences in the model you try but in
그들 중에서 당신은 당신이 시도 모델의하지만 약간의 차이를 알고 함께
general the same fundamental techniques work pretty well across all these
일반적으로는 같은 기본적인 기술은 모든 걸쳐 꽤 잘 작동
different domains and i'd give our results as a true you've heard about in
다른 도메인과 난 당신에 대해 들었어요 진정한 우리의 결과를 얻을 것
this class in lots of different areas now pretty much any computer vision
다른 지역의 제비에서이 클래스 이제 거의 모든 컴퓨터 비전
problem any speech problem these days starting to be more the case in lots of
문제는 이러한 일이 시작하는 음성 문제는 많은 더 많은 경우 일 수 있습니다
language understanding areas lots of kind of other areas of science like drug
약물과 같은 과학의 다른 영역의 종류의 언어 이해 영역의 많은
discovery are starting to have interesting role models that are better
발견은 더 나은 흥미로운 역할 모델을 가지고 시작
than alternate yeah I like them they're good along the way we've kind of built
다른 것보다 그래 나는 그들이 우리가 가지 내장 한 길을 따라 좋은있어 그들처럼
two different generations of our underlying system software for training
교육에 대한 우리의 기본 시스템 소프트웨어의 두 개의 서로 다른 세대
and deploying their lips the first was called disbelief republish paper about
자신의 입술을 배포하는 것은 처음이라고했다 불신 대해 논문을 게시
your nips 2012 it had the advantage of their was really scalable like the first
하여 닙 2012 그들의 장점은 제 등 실제로 확장이었다했다
one of the first uses we put to it was doing some unsupervised training I'll
우리가에 넣어 최초의 용도 중 하나는 내가거야 일부 자율 훈련을하고 있었다
tell you about a minute which used 16,000 course to training they don't
교육에 16,000 과정을 사용 분에 대해 말해 그들은하지 않습니다
have a lot of parameters is good for production use but it wasn't super
이 매개 변수가 많이 생산 사용에 적합하지만 슈퍼 아니었다
flexible for research like it was kinda hard to express kind of weird or more
이 종류의 이상한 이상의 표현하기 좀 어려운처럼 연구를위한 유연한
esoteric kinds of models reinforcement learning algorithms be hard to express
표현하는 모델 강화 학습 알고리즘의 비의 종류는 어렵다
and it had this kind of much more later driven approach with up-and-down
그리고 많은 이런 종류 이상 상하로 구동되는 방식을 가지고
messages and it worked well for what it did but we kind of took a step back
메시지와 그것이 무슨 짓을했는지 잘 작동하지만 우리는 종류의 다시 발을 내딛었
about a year and a little bit ago and started building our second generation
조금 전에 년에 대한 우리의 두 번째 세대를 구축 시작했다
system tends to flow which is based on what we learned the first generation and
시스템이 우리가 1 세대 배운 것을 기반으로하는 흐르는 경향과
what we learned from work and other sort of available open source packages and
우리가 작업하고있는 오픈 소스 패키지의 다른 종류에서 배운 무엇을
rethink its retained a lot of good features in disbelief but also made it
재고의 불신에 좋은 기능을 많이 유지뿐만 아니라 그것을 만든
pretty flexible for a wide variety of research is open source it which I got
연구의 다양한 꽤 유연 내가 가진 그것은 오픈 소스입니다
heard about one of the really nice properties have known that so I grabbed
정말 좋은 속성 중 하나에 대해 들어 그래서 내가 잡고 것으로 알려져있다
this from a particular paper cuz it had graphs on both scaling the sides of
이 모두 그래프의 측면을 확장했다 사촌 특정 논문에서이
training data and how accuracy increases and also scaling the size of the neural
트레이닝 데이터 및 방법의 정확성이 증가하고 또한 신경의 크기를 스케일링
net and how accuracy increases
그물 및 방법의 정확성 증가
exact details aren't important you can find these kinds of trends and hundreds
정확한 세부 사항은 중요하지 않습니다 당신은 트렌드와 수백 이러한 종류의를 찾을 수 있습니다
of papers but one of the really nice properties is if you have more data and
당신이 더 많은 데이터를 가지고있는 경우 그러나 논문의 정말 좋은 호텔 중 한 곳입니다
you can make your model bigger generally killing both of those things and even
당신은 당신의 모델이 일반적으로 이러한 것들을 모두 사망하고 더 큰 만들 수 있습니다
better than scaling just one of them you need a really big model in order to
단지 그들 중 하나를 확장보다 더 나은 당신은 순서대로 정말 큰 모델이 필요
capture kind of a more subtle trends that appear in larger and larger
더 큰에서 나타나는 미묘한 동향 캡처 종류
datasets you know any known that will capture kind of obvious trends or
데이터 세트가 어떤 종류의 명백한 트렌드를 포착 것이다 알려진 알거나
obvious kinda patterns but the more subtle ones are ones where you need a
당신이 필요로하는 곳에 분명 좀 패턴하지만 더 미묘한 것들 것들
bigger model to capture and if that extra she saw him too salty and that
그녀는 그를 너무 짠 것을보고 그 여분의 경우 더 큰 모델을 캡처하기
requires a lot more competition so we focus a lot on scaling the computation
우리가 계산을 확장에 많은 초점을 맞출 수 있도록 더 많은 경쟁이 필요합니다
we need and be able to train big models on big data sets to one of the first
우리가해야 할 첫 번째 중 하나에 큰 데이터 세트에 큰 모델을 훈련 할 수
things we did in this project was we said oh I'm surprised learning gonna be
우리는이 프로젝트에서했던 것을 우리가 아 내가 놀랄 배우고거야 수 말했다
really important and we had a big focus on that initially quickly and others
정말 중요하고 우리는 초기에 신속하게에 큰 초점을했고 다른 사람
said what would happen if we did unsupervised learning of random you to
우리가 임의의 당신을 자율 학습을했다면 무슨 일이 일어날 지했다
print so the idea is Rena take ten million random youtube frame single
아이디어가 레나가 천만 임의 유튜브 프레임 하나의 수행되도록 인쇄
frames from a bunch of random videos and we're going to essentially training data
임의의 동영상의 무리에서 프레임 우리는 본질적으로 데이터를 훈련하는거야
recorder everyone knows what color is that sounds like a family multi-level
레코더 모두가 그 가족 다단계 같은데 무슨 색깔입니다 알고
auto encoder you know and this one we're just trying to reconstruct the image now
자동차 당신이 알고 인코더와 우리가 지금 이미지를 재구성하려는이 하나
on we're trying to reconstruct the representation here from repetition
우리는 반복 여기서 표현을 재구성하려는에
there and so on and we used sixteen thousand cars we didn't have GPUs in the
이 등 우리가 만육천 자동차를 사용하여 우리는에서의 GPU가 없었다
datacenter the time so we compensated with light throwing more CPUs at it we
데이터 센터는 시간 그래서 우리는 빛이 더 많은 CPU를 던지고로 보상 우리
used a sink a cutie which will talk about a minute for optimization actually
실제로 최적화를위한 분에 대해 얘기하는 싱크 귀 염 둥이를 사용
had a lot of parameters cuz it was not convolutional this was prior to come we
이것은 우리를 와서 이전했다 길쌈되지 않은 그 사촌 매개 변수를 많이했다
should be all the rage so he said well we'll have a local receptive fields but
모든 분노를해야합니다 그는 또한 우리가 로컬 수용 필드를 가지고 있지만거야 말했다 있도록
they won't become delusional and will learn like separate representation for
그들은 망상가되지 않으며 별도의 표현처럼 배울 것
this part of the image in this part of the image which is kind of an
의 종류 이미지의이 부분에있는 이미지의이 부분
interesting twist I think it'd be actually an interesting experiment to
나는 그것이 실제로 흥미로운 실험이 될 거라고 생각 흥미로운 트위스트
redo this work but with convolutional opera sharing I'll be kind of cool in
이 작업을 다시 실행하지만, 길쌈 오페라 공유와 나는 서늘함의 종류에있을거야
any case the representation he learned the top after like nine layers
어떤 경우는 표현은 그와 같은 후 아홉 층 상단을 배웠다
of these non convolutional local receptive field $60,000 on the top level
이러한 비 길쌈 로컬 수용 필드의 최상위에 $ 60,000
and one of the things we thought might happen is it would learn kind of
우리가 일어날 거라고 생각 것들 중 하나는 가지 배울 것입니다
high-level feature detectors so in particular printing in pixels but it
높은 수준의 기능 픽셀 때문에 특히 인쇄에 감지기하지만,
couldn't learn high-level concepts we had a dataset that was half faces and
높은 수준의 개념을 배울 수있는 우리는 반 얼굴이었다 데이터 집합을 가지고 있었고,
have not faces and we found looked around for neurons that were good
하지면을 가지고 우리는 좋은 뉴런을 위해 주위를 둘러 보았다 발견
selectors of whether or not the image but estimates contained a face and we
하는지 여부, 이미지의 추정치 선택기 얼굴을 포함 우리
found several such neurons the best one that are those are some of the sample
몇 가지 예 뉴런을 수있는 최선의 일을 볼 수있는 샘플의 일부입니다
images that caused that neuron to get the most excited and then if you look
당신이 보면 신경이 후 가장 흥분을 얻을 수 있다는 인한 이미지
around for what stimulus will cause the neuron to get the most excited there's
주위의 원인이됩니다 어떤 자극에 대한 신경은 가장 흥분 거기에 도착
creepy face guy and that kind of interesting like we did had no labels on
소름 얼굴 남자와 재미의 종류는 우리가에는 라벨이 없었다처럼
the image in the dataset at all that we're training and a neuron in this
모든 데이터 셋의 이미지를 우리가 훈련하고 있다는이의 신경 세포
model has picked up on the fact that faces are things I'm gonna get excited
모델은 얼굴이 일이 내가 흥분거야 있다는 사실을 포착했다
when I see kind of a Caucasian face from head on its YouTube so we also have a
나는 그 YouTube에서 머리에서 백인 얼굴의 종류를 볼 때 우리는 또한이
cat now on a dataset with have captain have not kept in this is average tabby I
선장이 유지되지 않은 한과 데이터 집합에 지금 고양이는 평균 얼룩 무늬 I입니다
call them and then you can take that unsupervised model and and start a
그들에게 전화 한 다음 해당 자율 모델을 수 및 시작
supervised training tasks in particular at this time we were i training on the
이 때 특히 감독 훈련 작업은 우리 온 내가 훈련을했다
image next twenty thousand class task which is not the one the most damage
가장 손상 하나없는 이미지 스물 다음 천 클래스 작업
that results are reported on that one thousand classes is trying to
결과는 그 천 클래스에보고하려고하고있는
distinguish any made from one of 20 to 20,000 classes it's much harder task and
훨씬 더 열심히 작업의 모든 20 20,000 클래스 중 하나에서 만든 구별
then we trained and then looked around at what kinds of images cause different
우리는 다른 원인이 이미지의 종류에 주위를 둘러 보았다 다음 훈련
popular routes to get excited you see they're picking up on very high-level
인기있는 노선은 그들은 매우 높은 수준에 따기있어보고 흥분하는
concepts you know yellow flowers only or waterfowl
개념은 당신이 노란 꽃 전용 또는 물새 알
I like and this retraining actually increase the state to be hard accuracy
내가 좋아하는이 재교육 실제로 하드 정확도로 상태를 증가
on that particular task for amount at the time
시 양 특정 태스크에
then we kind of lost our excitement about unsupervised learning because
우리는 종류의 자율 학습 때문에 대한 우리의 흥분을 잃었다
supervised learning to cook so darn well and so we started working with a speech
그래서 이놈 잘 요리를 배우고 그래서 우리는 말과 ​​함께 작업을 시작 감독
team who at the time was had a non-parole Matt based acoustic
시 아닌 계 탄성 매트 가석방이었다 팀
essentially trying to go from a small segment of audio data like a hundred and
기본적으로 백처럼 오디오 데이터의 작은 세그먼트에서 이동하려고
fifty millisecond time you try to predict what sound does being uttered in
오십 밀리 초 시간은 당신이 소리에 선포되고 무엇을 예측하려고
the middle 10 milliseconds and so we just decided to try a layer fully
중간 10 밀리 초는 그리고 우리는 완전히 층을 바꾸기로했습니다
connected nomads and then predict one of fourteen thousand try phones at the top
유목민 접속하고 상단 만사천 시도 된 전화 중 하나를 예측
I'm at work family while basically could train it pretty quickly and it gave a
나는 기본적으로 매우 신속하게 훈련 할 수있는 동안 작업 가족에있어 그리고 그것은했다
huge reduction a moderate like this is one of the people on speech team said
거대한 감소 같은 온건 한 음성 팀에있는 사람들 중 하나가 말했다입니다
that like the biggest single improvement they've seen in their 20 years of
가장 큰 하나의 개선과 같은 그들의 20 년에 본 적이 있는지
research and that launched as part of the Android based search system 2012 so
연구와 그 안드로이드 기반 검색 시스템 2012 정도의 일환으로 시작
one of the things we often do is find that we have a lot of data for some
우리가 흔히하는 일 중 하나는 우리가 어떤 데이터를 많이 가지고 찾을 수있다
tasks but not very many very much data from the tasks and so for that we often
그에 대한 작업 등의 작업을하지만, 아주 많지 않은 매우 많은 데이터를 우리는 자주
deploy systems that make you sad multitask and transfer learning in
당신에게 슬픈 멀티 태스크를 확인하고 학습 전송 시스템을 구축
various ways so let's look at an example where we use this in speech so obviously
여러 가지 방법이 그래서는 우리가 분명히 연설에서 이것을 사용하는 예를 살펴 보자
with English we have a lot of data and we got a really nice slow word or it
영어로 우리는 많은 데이터를 가지고 있고 우리는 그것을 정말 좋은 느린 단어를 가지고 또는
lowers that are for Portuguese on the other hand about time we didn't have
반면에, 포르투갈어있다 저하는 시간에 대해 우리는하지 않았다
that much training today we had $100 purchase until the word error rate is a
단어 오류율이를 때까지 그 정도 훈련 오늘 우리는 $ (100) 구매를했다
lot worse which is bad so one of the first and most simple things you can do
그래서 당신이 할 수있는 첫 번째이자 가장 간단한 것들 중 하나 나쁜 더 많은
which is kind of what you do when you take a model has been pre trained on
이는 당신이 모델을 사전에 훈련 된 찍을 때 당신이하는 일의 종류
imaging that and apply to some other problem we don't have as much data as
및 다른 문제에 적용 촬상 우리는 많은 데이터가없는
you just start training with those weights by them totally random nights
당신은 그들을 완전히 무작위 밤에 의해 그 무게 훈련을 시작
I'm not actually improves your word error rate for Portuguese if it does
나는 실제로 않는 경우 포르투갈어 워드 에러율을 향상하고 있지 않다
there's enough similarities in the kinds of features you want for speech in
당신이 연설에 대해 원하는 기능의 종류에 충분한 유사성이있다
general regardless of language no more complicated thing you can do is actually
일반적으로는 언어에 상관없이 당신이 할 수있는 더 복잡한 것은 사실이다
jointly train models that share of entrepreneurs across all languages or in
공동 모든 언어에서 또는에서 모델에게 기업의 점유율을 훈련
this case all
이 경우 모든
all European languages I think it's what we used and so they are you see we're
모든 유럽 언어 나는 우리가 사용한 무엇을 생각하고 그래서 그들은 우리가있어 볼 수 있습니다
jointly training on this data and we actually got a pretty significant
공동으로이 데이터를 훈련하고 우리가 실제로 꽤 상당한있어
improvement even over the just copying the date of the Portuguese model but
심지어 포르투갈 모델의 단지 복사하는 일을 통해 개선하지만,
surprisingly we actually got a small improvement English because in total
놀랍게도 우리는 실제로 총 때문에 작은 개선이 영어를 얻었다
across all the other languages we actually almost double the amount of
다른 모든 언어를 통해 우리는 실제로는 거의 양을 두 배로
training data we were able to use you miss model compared to just English
교육 자료는 우리는 당신이 단지 영어에 비해 모델을 그리워 사용할 수 있었다
alarm so basically like languages without much dated all improved a lot
많은 일없이 그렇게 기본적으로 언어와 같은 알람이 모두 많이 향상
languages with a lot of data improved even a little bit and then we had a
데이터의 많은 언어를 조금이라도 개선하고 우리는 있었다
language-specific top layer little little bit of fiddling to figure out
알아낼 하구의 언어 별 최상층 조금 조금
does it make some tough to language specific top players 1 I'll believe
그것은 언어 별 최고 선수 일부가 힘든 만들 않는 한 나는 믿을거야
these are the kinds of human guided choices you are making
이들은 당신이 만들고 인간의 가이드 선택의 종류가
that's the production speech models involved a lot from those really simple
즉, 생산 음성 모델은 그 정말 간단에서 많이 참여의
feedforward models used now I last came to deal with time to mention the
지금 사용하는 피드 포워드 모델은 내가 마지막으로 언급 할 시간을 처리했다
compilation of allusions to make them in very into different frequencies so there
암시의 컴파일 그래서이 매우 다른 주파수로 그들을 만들려면
was a paper published here you know you don't necessarily need to understand all
종이 여기에 출판되었다​​ 당신은 반드시 모든 이해 할 필요가 없습니다 알고
the details but there's a lot of more complexity in the kind of model and it's
상세하지만이 모델의 종류에 더 많은 복잡성은이고 그것의
it's using much more sophisticated her current models and computational models
그것은 그녀의 현재 모델과 계산 모델 훨씬 더 정교한을 사용하고
a recent trend has been met you can use alice is completely and and so rather
최근의 추세는 앨리스가 완전히 그래서 오히려 사용할 수 있습니다 충족 된
than having an acoustic model and then a language model that kind of takes the
이러한 종류의 소요 음향 모델 후 언어 모델을 갖는보다
output of the acoustic model of an estranged somewhat separately you can go
소외의 음향 모델의 출력은 다소 별도로 갈 수
directly from audio waveforms to producing transcript to character at a
직접 오디오 파형에서에서 문자로 성적 증명서를 생산하는
time and I think that's going to be a really big trend
시간과 그게 정말 큰 트렌드가 될 것 같아
both in speech and more generally in a lot of heating systems you often have
모두 연설에서 더 일반적으로 난방 시스템을 많이에서 당신은 종종이
today a lot of systems are kind of composed of a bunch of subsystems each
오늘은 많은 시스템이 가지 서브 시스템 각각의 무리로 구성되어 있습니다
perhaps with some she learned pieces and some kind of hand coded pieces and then
아마도 일부 그녀는 조각과 손 코드 조각의 일부 종류를 배웠다
I usually a big pile of goo decode to glue it all together and
나는 보통 끈적 거리는 디코드의 큰 더미가 모두 함께 접착제 및
and often although separately developed pieces have impediments optimization
별도로 개발 한 조각 장애 최적화가 종종 있지만,
right like you optimize your subsystem in the context of symmetric by that
당신은에 의해 대칭의 맥락에서 서브 시스템을 최적화 오른쪽처럼
metric might not be the right thing for the final task you care about which
통계는 어떤 관심있는 마지막 작업을 위해 옳은 일을하지 않을 수 있습니다
might be transcribed correctly so having a much bigger single system like a
올바르게 복사 할 수 있으므로 같은 훨씬 더 큰 하나의 시스템을 가지고
single neural Apple goes directly from audio waveform all the way to the end
하나의 신경 애플은 끝까지 오디오 파형에서 직접 모든 길을 간다
objective you care about prescription and that you cannot optimize end-to-end
목표는 당신이 처방에 관심 당신은 엔드 - 투 - 엔드를 최적화 할 수 없음
through and there's not a lot of hand written code in the middle that is going
통해가는 중간에 손으로 쓴 많은 코드가 아니다
to be a big trend I think you'll see that here you'll see that I'm missing
난 당신이 내가 부족 것을 볼 수 있습니다 여기에 볼 수있을 거라 생각 큰 트렌드가 될 수 있습니다
translation a lot of other kinds of demands so who's all competitions we
번역 요구의 다른 종류의 많은 그래서 사람들은 모든 대회의 우리
have tons of vision problems that we've been using various kinds of
우리는 다양한 종류를 사용했던 시력 문제의 톤을 가지고
computational models for you know the big excitement around convolutional
당신을위한 계산 모델은 길쌈 주위에 큰 흥분을 알고
neural nets well first it started with young and check reading competition that
신경망 잘 먼저 젊은 시작과 경쟁을 읽고 확인하는 것이
kind of like subsided for a while and then Alex Kozinski yo yo sup favor and
가지 잠시 가라 앉았하고 좋아 다음 알렉스 Kozinski 요 요 한모금의 은혜와
check for him to paper in 2012 which light blue the other competitors out of
에서 블루에게 다른 경쟁에 불을하는 2012 년 종이에 그를 확인
the water in the image net 2012 challenge using a non that I think put
내가 넣어 생각 비를 사용하여 이미지 순이익 2,012 도전에 물
those things on everyone's map again saying well we should we should be using
모든 사람의지도에 그 일이 다시 우리는 우리가 사용되어야한다 잘 말
these things for vision cuz they work really well and the next year
그들은 정말 잘 작동 사촌 비전이 일 내년
something like twenty twenty of the entries or something you know not
항목의 스물 스물이나 뭐 같은 당신은 알지
threads previously it was just Alex we've had a bunch of people at Google
스레드는 이전에 그냥 알렉스 우리는 구글에서 사람들의 무리 했어했다
looking at various kinds of architectures for doing better and
더 나은 일을 위해 아키텍처의 다양한 종류의보고
better image that consultations on the inspection architecture has like this
검사 아키텍처에 대한 협의는 다음과 같이 가지고 더 나은 이미지
complicated model of like different size competitions that are all kind of
모든 종류의 수 있습니다 같은 다른 크기 경쟁의 복잡한 모델
concatenated together and then you can't replicate those models a bunch of times
함께 연결된 후, 당신은 그 모델에게 시간의 무리를 복제 할 수 없습니다
and
과
you end up with a very deep known at that turned out to be quite good at it
그게 꽤 좋은 밝혀졌다에서 당신은 매우 깊은 알려진 끝낼
condition there's been some slight additions to that and slight changes to
조건은 어떤 것과 약간의 추가 및에 약간의 변화가있었습니다
make it even more accurate you know I have you seen a slight like that in like
그것은 훨씬 더 정확한 당신처럼 내가 당신이 그런 식으로 약간을 보았다 알고 있어야합니다
okay so I I was lazy susan only took my slides from a folder thing I ever told
좋아 그래서 II가 게을 렀다는 수잔 만 내가 이야기 폴더 일에서 내 슬라이드를했다
the story about Andre sitting down on him labeling
그 라벨에 앉아 앙드레 대한 이야기
ok signing Andrei decided he was helping to administer the image that contest he
확인 안드레이는 자신이 이미지를 그 대회를 관리하는 데 도움이되었다 결정에 서명 그는
would sit down and subject himself 200 hours of training training training
앉아서 자신을 훈련 교육 훈련 200 시간을 가하지 것
tough split and like this at an Australian Shepherd Dog I don't know and
나도 몰라 오스트레일리아 양치기 개에서이 같은 힘든 분할 및 및
yes I can convince one of the lab mates to do it but they weren't intelligence
예 나는 그것을 할 수있는 실험실 동료 중 하나를 설득 할 수 있지만 지능 없었다
are heated about a hundred and twenty hours of training on images
이미지에 대한 교육의 백 이십시간에 대해 가열
and his lab may get tired after 12 hours or something so he got 5.1 percent error
그의 연구실은 그가 5.1 %의 오류가있어 있도록 12 시간 일 후 피곤받을 수 있습니다
made got I think 12%
제작 내가 12 %를 생각있어
human error but without rain badly all over the weekend
인간의 오류하지만 비없이 심하게 모든 주말
back at one hundred and twelve hours later whatever anyway here is a great
뒤쪽에 백십이시간 나중에 어쨌든 여기에 좋은 무엇이든
blog post about it I encourage you to check it out he has a lot of parameters
그것에 대해 블로그 게시물 나는 그가 매개 변수를 많이 가지고 확인해 보시기 바랍니다
so typical humans are like you know 80 trillion connection that many 201 one
당신이 많은 201 일이 80000000000000 연결을 알고 같은 전형적인 인간은
point about these models as the models of a small number of parameters fit well
파라미터 소수의 모델에 잘 맞는 이들 모델에 대한 지적
on my mobile devices so I'm doesn't fit while on a mobile phone but the general
내 모바일 장치에서 난 휴대 전화 있지만 일반에 다소 맞지 않도록
trend other than andre is like smaller numbers of parameters compared to Alex
앙드레 이외의 추세는 알렉스에 비해 매개 변수의 작은 숫자처럼
mostly Alex net had like these two giant fully connected layers of the top that
대부분 알렉스 그물 상단이이 두 거대한 완전히 연결 층 같이했다
giant but a lot of parameters and later worked just kind of get away with it was
그것이 함께 거대한하지만 매개 변수를 많이 이상은 가지 얻을 멀리했다
the most part and so they've used you know a small number of parameters but
대부분의과가 그래서 그들은 당신이 매개 변수의 작은 번호를 알고 사용했지만
more floating point operations per use compositional parameters mark which is
이다 사용 조성 매개 변수 표시 당 부동 소수점 연산
good for putting them on funds we released as part of the tensor flow
좋은 펀드에 이르렀 우리는 텐서 흐름의 일부로 출시
update up retrain adoption model which you can use there's an editorial about
당신이 사설에 대한 거기에 사용할 수있는 재시도 채택 모델을 업데이트
it there is Chris Harper although we think its military uniform which is not
우리가하지 않은 군사 유니폼을 생각하지만, 그것은 크리스 하퍼가
terribly inaccurate one of the nice things about these models as they're
그들이있어 이러한 모델에 대한 좋은 것들을 몹시 부정확 한
really good at doing very fine-grained consultations I think one of the things
아주 세밀한 상담을하고 정말 좋은 나는 것들 중 하나라고 생각
that is an Andres blog is that the computer models are actually much much
이 컴퓨터 모델은 훨씬 실제로 있다는 안드레스 블로그입니다
better than people at distinguishing exact breeds of dogs but humans are
개 그러나 인간이다의 구별 정확한 품종에서 사람보다 더 나은
better at
더 나은
often picking out a small you know if if the label is ping pong ball and it's
자주 레이블이 탁구 공이며 경우가 있다면 당신이 알고있는 작은을 따기
like a giant senior people playing ping pong humans are better at that
탁구 인간을 재생하는 거대한 고위 사람들처럼 그에서 더 낫다
models tend to focus on things with more pixels if you train models with the
모델은 당신이있는 모델을 훈련하면 더 많은 픽셀 일에 집중하는 경향이
right kind of data
데이터의 오른쪽 종류
you know generalize while these scenes look nothing alike but they actually you
이러한 장면은 모두 아무것도 보지 동안 일반화 알고 있지만 실제로 당신
know we'll both get labeled as me love your training data is represented well
우리는 모두 당신의 훈련 데이터를 사랑 나를로 표시거야 알고 잘 표현된다
they make an acceptable errors which kinda nineties no it's not a snake but
그들은 그것이 뱀이 아니다 좀 더 구십 허용 실수를하지만,
you understand why am I just said that and I know it's not a dog but I actually
난 그냥 그런 말을하고 왜 이해하고 난 개가 아니에요 알고 있지만 실제로 I
had to think carefully if the front animal there is a is a donkey and I'm
전면 동물이이 당나귀가되고 난 경우 신중하게 생각했다
still not entirely sure
완전히 확실하지 아직도
any votes so one of the production uses we've put these kinds of models kiryas
모든 투표는 이렇게 생산 중 하나는 우리가 모델 kiryas의 이러한 종류를 넣었습니다 사용합니다
Google photo search so we launched Google photo product and you can search
구글 사진 검색 그래서 우리는 Google 사진 제품을 출시하면 검색 할 수 있습니다
the photos that you've uploaded without talking about all you just type ocean
방금 바다 입력 한 모든 얘기하지 않고 업로드 한 사진
and all of a sudden oliver ocean Photoshop so for example this user
갑자기 올리버 바다 포토샵의 모든 그래서 예를 들어이 사용자에 대한
posted publicly hey I posted a screenshot hey I didn't take these
공개적으로 게시 헤이 나는 스크린 샷 헤이 나는이 걸릴하지 않았다 게시
statues of Buddha showed up for city driving you know this is a tough because
부처님의 동상이 때문에 힘든 것을 알고 도시 운전을위한 나타났다
it got a lot of textured compared to most Utahns so we're pretty pleased to
대부분의 Utahns에 비해 질감이 많이 그래서 우리는 꽤 기쁘게 생각있어
retrieve macrophage others we have a lot of kind of other kinds of more specific
우리가보다 구체적인 다른 종류의 종류의 많은이 대 식세포 등을 검색
visual tasks like essentially one of the things we want to do in our Street View
우리는 우리의 스트리트 뷰에서하고 싶은 것들을 본질적으로 같은 비주얼 작업
imagery of these cars the driver in the world and take pictures of all the roads
세계에서이 차 운전자의 이미지와 모든 도로의 사진을 촬영
and street scenes and then we want to be able to read all the texts that we find
거리 장면과 그 다음 우리는 우리가 찾을 수있는 모든 텍스트를 읽을 수 있어야합니다
so first you have to find the text and well one of the first thing you want to
그래서 먼저 당신이 원하는 우선의 텍스트와 잘 하나를 찾을 수있다
do is find all the addresses and maps and months ago that you wanna like read
이렇게하면 읽기처럼 싶은 것을 전 모든 주소와지도와 달을 찾을 수 있습니다
all the other texts so you can see that it doesn't we have a model that does a
당신이 우리가을하는 모델이없는 것을 볼 수 있도록 다른 모든 텍스트
pretty good job of predicting that a pixel level which which pixels contain
예측 꽤 좋은 직장 그 화소가 포함되는 픽셀 수준
text or not and does pretty well in
텍스트 여부와 꽤 잘하지
well first of all finds lots of tax in the training data had different kinds of
잘 우선 훈련 데이터에 세금을 많이 발견은 여러 종류가 있었다
characters that represented so it has no problem recognizing Chinese characters
이렇게 표시되는 문자는 더 문제가 한자를 인식하지 않았다
English characters are Roman Latin characters it does pretty well like
영어 문자는 꽤 잘처럼 수행 로마 라틴 문자이다
different colors of of tax two different fonts and sizes and some of them are
세금의 두 개의 서로 다른 글꼴과 크기와 그들 중 몇 가지의 서로 다른 색상
very close to the cameras are very far away and i was just and this is data
이다 매우 멀리 떨어져 카메라에 매우 근접하고 난 그냥이었고,이 데이터입니다
from just human labeled drawn polygons around pieces of text and then they
텍스트의 조각 주위에 단지 인간의 표지 그린 다각형에서 그리고 그들은
transcribed it and then we have an OCR model we also print
다음을 전사하고 우리가 OCR 모델을 우리 또한 인쇄
we've been kind of gradually releasing other kinds of products we just launched
우리는 가지 점차적으로 우리가 출시 제품의 다른 종류를 출시했습니다
cloud vision of ATI's you can do lots of things like label images this is meant
ATI의의 클라우드 비전은 당신이 의미 라벨 이미지 같은 것들을 많이 할 수 있습니다
for people who don't necessarily wanna want or how machine learning expertise I
반드시 싶어하지 않는 사람 또는 방법을 기계 학습 전문 I에 대한
just kind of want to do cool stuff with images you want to go to you know say
단지 종류의 당신이 말을 알고에 가고 싶어 이미지와 함께 멋진 물건을하고 싶지
only that they're running seemed to do the OCR and find taxed in any image
그들은 OCR을 수행하고 모든 이미지에서 과세 찾을 것 같았다 실행하는 경우에만 있음
uploads you just basically given an emergency a bike Toronto CRM label
당신은 기본적으로 자전거 토론토 CRM 라벨 비상 사태를 부여 업로드
generation of this image and if it goes to people have been pretty happy with
이 사람에게가는 경우이 이미지의 생성과 꽤 행복했다
that
그
internally people have been thinking of more creative uses of how to use
내부적으로 사람들이 사용하는 방법의 창조적 사용을 생각하고있다
computer vision essentially now that computer vision sort of really actually
컴퓨터 비전 정말 실제로 본질적으로 지금 컴퓨터 비전 정렬
works compared to five years ago this is something that our our our geo team that
오년에 비해 작품 전에이 일이 우리의 우리의 우리 지역 팀입니다
process and satellite imagery put together and released which is basically
기본적으로 어떤 프로세스와 위성 이미지를 함께 넣어 출시
a way of predicting the slope of roofs from multiple satellite views of that
그 여러 위성 뷰에서 지붕의 기울기를 예측하는 방법
country you'd like have you know every few months new satellite imagery here
국가 당신은 당신이 여기에 몇 개월마다 새로운 위성 이미지를 알고있다 싶습니다
until we have multiple views of the same location and we can predict what the
우리가 같은 위치의 여러 전망이 때까지 우리는 무엇을 예측할 수있다
slope of the roof is given all those different views of the same location and
지붕의 기울기가 같은 위치의 모든 다른 견해를 제공하고,
how much sun exposure to get out and then predict you know if you were to
나가 다음 당신이 인 경우에 당신이 알고 예측하는 방법 많은 태양 노출
install solar panels anyhow how much energy could you generated by getting
당신이 점점 생성 할 수 얼마나 많은 에너지 어쨌든 태양 전지 패널을 설치
kinda cool you know it's like a small random things you can do not a vision
좀 당신이 당신이 할 수있는 작은 임의의 물건이 아닌 비전처럼 알고 냉각
works ok so this class has been mostly mostly about vision so I'm gonna talk
작동 확인이 클래스는 내가 거 얘기 해요 그래서 대부분은 대부분의 비전에 대해되었습니다
now about other kinds of problems like language understanding one of the most
이제 언어 이해 같은 문제의 다른 종류에 대한 가장 중 하나
important problems is search obviously so we care a lot about surgery and in
중요한 문제는 분명히 검색 그래서 우리는 수술에 대한과에 많은 관심입니다
particular if I do the query car parts for sale I'd like to determine which of
내가 판매에 대한 쿼리 자동차 부품을한다면 내가 확인하고 싶은 특정의 어떤
these two documents is more relevant and you just look at the service forms of
이 두 문서는 관련성 그리고 당신은 단지의 서비스 형태를 보면
the word that first document looks pretty darn relevant
첫 번째 문서는 무척 관련 보이는 것을 말씀
like lots of the words occur autorad but actually the second document is much
단어를 많이처럼 발생은 autorad 실제로 두 번째 문서는 많이 있습니다
more relevant given that and we'd like to be able to understand that so how
관련성이 주어 우리는 어떻게 그래서 이해할 수 있도록하고 싶습니다
much have you talked about embedding model awesome so you know about the
당신이에 대해 알 수 있도록 많은 당신이 멋진 모델을 포함 이야기가
medics
의료진
embedding defendants to so I will go quickly but basically you want to
피고인을 포함하는 것은 그래서 나는 빨리 갈 것입니다하지만 기본적으로 당신이 원하는합니다
represent words or things in high-dimensional things that are sparse
드문 드문 높은 차원 일에 단어 나 사물을 표현
map them into a dense case some hundred dimension 11,000 dimensional space so
조밀 한 경우 몇 백 차원 11,000 차원 공간 때문에로 매핑
that you can now have things that are near each other and have similar
이제 서로 가까이와 유사한이 일을 가질 수
meanings will end up near each other in the high-dimensional spaces so for
의미에 대한 너무 높은 차원 공간에서 서로 가까이 끝날 것
example you might porpoises and dolphins to be very near each other in the
예를 들어 당신은 돌고래와 돌고래는 매우 가까이 서로 될 수 있습니다
high-dimensional space because they're quite similar words and have some
그들은 매우 유사 단어이고 어떤을 가지고 있기 때문에 높은 차원 공간
meetings they share the same time the purpose
회의 그들은 목적 동시에 공유
ok
그래
and SeaWorld you be kind of nearby and Cameron parents to be pretty far away
와 씨월드 당신은 가지 근처의 수와 카메론의 부모는 꽤 멀리로
and you can train embedding to modernize one is to have it kind of is the first
당신이 하나를 현대화 포함 훈련 할 수는 최초 인 것입니다
thing you do when you're feeding get into and out of steam and even simpler
당신이로 스팀에서, 심지어 간단한 GET을 공급 할 때 당신이 할 일
thing is a technique my former colleague too much nickel off came up with the be
일은 나의 전 동료 너무 많은 니켈 오프가 될 해낸 기술이다
published paper about where essentially it's called the word to make model and
이 모델을 만들기 위해 단어라고 어디 본질적으로 대한 출판 종이
essentially you pick up window of words maybe twenty words why did you pick the
아마 스무 단어가 왜 당신이를 선택 않았다 기본적으로 당신은 단어의 창을 선택
center word and then you pick another random where do try to use the embedding
워드 센터 및 다음 삽입을 사용하려고 할 경우 다른 랜덤을 선택
representation of that center word to predict a man you can train that hoping
그 중심 단어의 표현은 그 희망을 훈련 할 수있는 사람을 예측하는
the backdrop essentially you adjust the weights muscle flex classifier and then
배경으로는 기본적으로 당신은 그 무게의 근육 플렉스 분류를 조정하고
in turn you through backpropagation you you make little adjustments to the
결과적으로 당신은 역 전파을 통해 당신은 거의 조정
embedding representation of that center word so that next time you'll be able to
그 중심 단어의 표현을 포함하는 다음 번에 ​​할 수 있습니다 있도록
better predict the word parts from automobile and actually works right like
더 나은 자동차에서 단어 부분을 예측하고 실제로 오른쪽처럼 작동
one of the really nice things about abetting the is given enough training
을 선동에 대한 정말 좋은 것 중 하나는 충분한 교육을 제공됩니다
did you got really phenomenal weapons visions of words so these are the
이들은 그래서 당신이 단어의 정말 놀라운 무기 비전을 가지고 않았다
nearest neighbors for these three different words or phrases as vocabulary
어휘 이러한 세 가지 다른 단어 나 문구에 대한 가장 가까운 이웃
items in this particular on the tiger shark you can think of his 11 embedding
호랑이 상어에이 특정 항목 당신은 자신의 11 삽입 생각할 수
vector and these are the nearest neighbors say it it got the center of
이들 벡터는 가장 가까운 이웃은 그 중심을 가지고 말
sharpness car is interesting right like you see why this is useful for search
이 검색에 유용 이유를 볼 같은 선명도 자동차 흥미 권리가있다
because you have things that people often hand coded information retrieval
당신이 일이 있기 때문에 사람들은 종종 코딩 정보 검색을 건네 것을
systems like plurals and stemming and like some kind of simple synonyms but
복수형 및 형태소 분석 등의 간단한 동의어 어떤 종류의 같은 시스템 만
here he just seemed like oh I know car automobile pickup truck racing car
여기에 그는 단지 오 내가 자동차 자동차 픽업 트럭 경주 용 자동차를 알고 같은 듯
passenger car dealership is kind of related you just see that has this this
여객 자동차 대리점의 종류 당신은 그냥이이이 참조 관련
right concept of a knife Kenneth smooth representation of car rather than
바로 자동차의 칼 케네스 부드러운 표현의 개념이 아닌
explicitly only the latter see our match that and it turns out that if you
명시 적으로 만 후자는 우리의 경기를 관람하며 밝혀 당신 경우
trained using the word avec approach that directions turn out to be
방향으로 판명 단어 AVEC 접근 방식을 사용하여 훈련
meaningful and mental spaces so not only is proximity interesting but directions
의미 있고 정신적 인 공간이 너무뿐만 아니라 근접 재미 있지만, 방향이다
are interesting so it turns out if you look at
흥미로운 그래서 당신이 보면 그것은 밝혀
capital and country pairs you go
자본과 국가 쌍 가고
roughly the same direction and distance to get from a country with corresponding
거의 같은 방향과 거리가 대응하는 국가에서 얻을 수
capital or vice versa for any country capital Paris and you also can you see
파리, 당신은 또한 당신이 볼 수있는 국가 자본에 대한 자본 또는 그 반대의 경우도 마찬가지
some semblance of other structures is the embeddings map down to two
다른 구조의 일부 외관이 묻어 두 아래지도입니다
dimensions the principal components analysis so and you see kind of
그래서 주성분 분석을 치수 당신은 종류의 참조
interesting structures around verb tenses regardless of the firm which
동사의 주위에 흥미 구조는 회사에 관계없이 시제하는
means you can solve analogies like queen is decaying as well mister man by doing
당신은 여왕처럼 유추을 수행하여뿐만 아니라 아저씨 사람이 부패되어 해결할 수 있음을 의미
some simple fact arithmetic say you're literally just looking at the embedding
몇 가지 간단한 사실 연산은 말 그대로 그냥 삽입보고있는 말
vector and then adding the difference to get to that point approximately the
차이를 추가 벡터 한 다음 그 지점에 거의 도착
point so we've been in collaboration with the search team we launched kind of
그래서 우리는 우리가 가지 시작 검색 팀과 공동으로 봤는데 포인트
one of the biggest search ranking changes in the last few years we called
우리라는 지난 몇 년 동안에서 가장 큰 검색 순위 중 하나가 변경
it rang bringing essentially just a deep know that but uses embeddings and a
그것은 단지 깊은 알고 본질적으로 데려 울렸다하지만 묻어 및 사용
bunch of players to give you a score for how relevant this document is for this
선수의 무리가이 문서는이 것이 얼마나 중요한에 대한 점수를주고
particular
특별한
and it's the third most important for train travel miles out of hundreds of
그것은 수백 중 기차 여행 마일 세 번째 가장 중요한
that so-called smart reply was a little cooperation with the Gmail team were
그 소위 스마트 응답은 Gmail 팀과 함께 약간의 협력이 있었다이었다
essentially replying to mail on your phone kind of sucks cuz typing is hard
기본적으로 휴대 전화에 메일을 회신 종류의 사촌 입력이 어렵다 짜증
and so we wanted to have a system where often you can predict what would be a
그래서 우리는 당신이 될 것이라고 예측할 수 종종 시스템을 가지고 싶어
good reply just looking at the message so we have a small network the predicts
좋은 응답이 바로 메시지를 찾고 그래서 우리는 소규모 네트워크가이 예측이
is that a likely to be something that I can have a short terse response to see
수있는 가능성이 내가 볼 수있는 짧은 간결한 응답을 가질 수 뭔가를 할 수 있음
if you ask them i activate a much bigger
당신이 그들을 묻는다면 나는 훨씬 더 큰 활성화
model and this is a message one of my colleagues received a project that from
모델이 제 동료 중 하나가 프로젝트를 수신하는 메시지입니다에서
his brother he said we want to invite you to join us for an early Thanksgiving
그의 동생은 그는 우리가 이른 추수 감사절 우리와 함께 당신을 초대하고자했다
probable bob we've been your favorite dish RCP next week so then the model
가능성이 밥 우리는​​ 그래서 다음 모델 좋아하는 요리 RCP 다음 주에 봤는데
predicts countess and will be there or sorry won't be able to make it
백작을 예측하고있을 것 또는 죄송는 그것을 만들 수 없습니다
great if you get a lot of email it's fantastic although your replies will be
이메일을 많이받을 경우 응답이 될 것입니다하지만 좋은 그것은 환상적이다
somewhat curse of them which is nice
좋은 그들 중 다소 저주
you know we can do interesting things like this is a mobile app that actually
당신이 실제로 모바일 앱처럼 우리가 흥미있는 일을 할 수있어
runs in airplane mode so it's actually running the models on the phone and it's
비행기 모드에서 실행 그래서 실제로 전화 모델을 실행중인 그것은이다
actually got a lot of interesting things entirely realized so you're essentially
실제로 당신이 본질적으로있어, 그래서 완전히 실현 흥미로운 것들을 많이 가지고
using the camera image for detecting text in your finding what the words are
단어가 무엇인지 발견하여 텍스트를 검출하는 카메라 영상을 이용하여
doing OCR on it here then running it through a translation model you can
다음 여기에 OCR을 수행 할 수있는 번역 모델을 통해 그것을 실행
figure it in a particular about this is just cycling through different languages
이것에 대해, 특히 그것을 그림은 서로 다른 언어를 순환한다
but normally you'd set on Spanish money but only show you Spanish but the thing
그러나 일반적으로 당신은 스페인어 돈에 설정 거라고하지만 스페인어하지만 일이 보여
that in realizes there's actually an interesting fun selection problem like
점에서 흥미로운 재미 선택 문제 등이 실제로있다 실현
choose what I want to show you the output so kind of call good if you're
내가 그렇게 종류의 당신이 있다면 좋은 호출하면 출력을 보여주고 싶은 것을 선택
traveling
여행
interesting place I'm actually going to Korea untiring so I am i'm looking
흥미로운 장소는 사실은 그래서 내가 찾고 있어요 오전 한국 불굴 갈거야
forward to using my translator up as they don't be so one of the things we do
그들은 우리가하는 일이 너무 일하지 않는 나의 번역기를 사용하여 전달
a bit of work on is reducing insurance costs there's like nothing worse than
보험을 줄일 수 있습니다에 약간의 작업 비용 아무것도처럼보다 더있다
this feeling that wow my model is so awesome with great it's just sad dreams
와우 내 모델이 큰 너무 굉장이 느낌은 그냥 슬픈 꿈이야
my phone's battery in Germany
독일 내 휴대 전화의 배터리
or you know I can't afford the temptation to run it at you know I keep
또는 당신은 내가 당신은 내가 계속 알고 그것을 실행하는 유혹을 감당할 수있어
you in my data center even though I have gotten machines so there's lots of
많이있다, 그래서 내 데이터 센터의 당신은 내가 기계를받은 경우에도
tricks you can use in particular the simplest wanna news in for instance
당신은 예를 들어 특히 간단한 싶어 뉴스에서 사용할 수있는 트릭
generally much more forgiving of even much lower precision computation dan
심지어 훨씬 낮은 정밀 계산 단의 일반적으로 훨씬 더 관대
training so far in France we usually find we can quantized all the way to get
훈련은 지금까지 프랑스에서 우리는 일반적으로 우리가 얻을 수있는 모든 방법을 양자화 할 수 있습니다 발견
through even less a bit too sista nice quality but cheap you'd like to deal
더 적은 조금 너무 그녀 야 좋은 품질하지만 저렴한 통해 당신은 거래를하고 싶습니다
with really you could do six that's prolly but that doesn't help that much
정말 당신은 prolly의 육을 할 수 있지만 그 많은 도움이되지 않습니다
that gives you like a nice Forex memory reduction in storing the parameters and
그 매개 변수를 저장하기에 좋은 외환 메모리 감소처럼를 제공하고
also give you for a competition efficiency cuz you can use CPU vector
또한 CPU 벡터를 사용할 수 있습니다 사촌 경쟁 효율을 제공
instructions to 24 multiplies instead of 1:30 but why suddenly got to tell you
(24) 대신 1:30 곱하지만 왜 설명은 갑자기 당신에게있어
about kind of a cuter more exotic way of getting more efficiency out of a mobile
모바일에서 더 많은 효율을 얻기의 귀엽 더 이국적인 방법의 종류에 대한
phone
전화
the technique called distillation that jeffrey hinton organelles and I worked
제프리 힌튼의 세포 소기관 내가 근무하는 기술이라고 증류
on so suppose you have a really really giant model the problem I just described
그래서 생각에 당신은 정말 거대한 모델에게 난 그냥 설명하는 문제가
this fantastic model you really pleased with maybe of an ensemble of those and
어쩌면 이들의 앙상블과 함께 정말 기쁘게이 환상적인 모델 당신에게
now you want a smaller cheaper model at almost the same actors so here it is
지금 당신은 그래서 여기에 작은 싼 모델에서 거의 같은 배우를 원한다
your giant expensive model you feed the same agenda gives you fantastic
당신의 거대한 비싼 모델 동일한 의제는 환상적인 준다 공급
predictions like . 95 Jaguar I'm pretty sure and I'm definitely sure that's not
예측은 좋아한다. 95 재규어 나는 확신하고 나는 그것이 아니다 확실히 확신
a car
자동차
10-4 car window for you I'm heading to bed it could be a lion right so that's
당신을 위해 10-4 차 창은 내가 잘 그래서 그건 사자가 될 수 침대로 향하고 있어요
what I really accurate model do tell the main idea unfortunately we later
나중에 불행하게도 우리를 메인 아이디어를 말해 정말 정확한 모델을 무엇을
discovered the rich Caruana in 2006 had published a similar idea in a paper
2006 년 부자 카루 아나는 논문에서 비슷한 생각을 게시 발견했다
called model compression so the ensemble for your giant accurate model implements
당신의 거대한 정확한 모델 구현을위한 앙상블 소위 모델 압축
this interesting function from input-output so if you forget the fact
입력 - 출력에서​​이 흥미로운 기능은 사실을 잊어 버린 경우 이렇게
that there's some structure there and you just try to use the information
거기에 몇 가지 구조 그리고 당신은 정보를 사용하려고하는 것이
that's contained in that function how can we transfer the knowledge in that
그는 우리가있는 지식을 전달하는 방법을 그 함수에 포함 된 것
really accurate function into a smaller
작은에 정말 정확한 기능
intention of the function so when you're training a model typically what you do
함수의 의도는 그래서 당신은 당신이 무엇 일반적으로 모델을 훈련 할 때
is you feat an image like this and then you give it targets to try to the chief
당신 위업이 같은 이미지입니다 다음은 주요하려고하는 대상으로 제공
and you give it the target one Jaguar Land Rover everything else I'm gonna
당신은 내가거야 다른 대상에게 그것을 하나의 재규어 랜드 로버 모든 것을 제공
call that a hard target so that's kind of the ideal your model is striving to
그래서 하드 타겟이 모델에 노력하고 이상적인의 종류의 것을 호출
achieve and you give it you know hundreds of thousands or millions of
달성하고 당신은 수천 또는 수백만의 수백을 알고 그것을 제공
training images in a drive to approximate all these factors from the
드라이브의 이미지를 훈련하는 것은 모든 요인에 근접하는
differences in actual fact it doesn't quite do that cuz he gives you this nice
실제 사실에 차이가 꽤하지 않습니다 그는 당신이 좋은를 제공 사촌
public probability distribution over different images over different classes
다른 클래스를 통해 다른 이미지를 통해 공개 확률 분포
for the same marriage so let's take our giant expensive model and one of the
같은 결혼은 그래서 우리의 거대한 비싼 모델과 중 하나를 수행 할 수 있도록하기위한
things we can do is we can actually soften that distribution of it and this
우리가 할 수있는 일이 우리가 실제로이의 분포를 부드럽게 할 수있다
is what jeffrey hinton calls dark knowledge but if you soften this by
제프리 힌튼 어두운 지식을 부르는하지만 당신은이 작업을 부드럽게 경우
essentially dividing all the logistic units by a temperature to you might be
당신이있을 수 있습니다에 기본적으로 온도에 의해 모든 물류 단위를 분할
like five or ten or something you then get a softer representation of this
5 ~ 10 개 무엇인가 당신은이의 부드러운 표현을 얻을
probability distribution where you say okay at the Jaguar but also kinda hedge
당신은 재규어에 괜찮 말할뿐만 아니라 좀 회피 확률 분포
about the little and call it a bit of a lion maybe even less of a cow still call
에 대한 작은 여전히​​ 전화 소 어쩌면 작은 사자의 비트를 호출
it definitely not a car and that's something you can then years and this
그것은 확실히 자동차와 그 당신이 다음 년 수 뭔가이
fall distribution made a lot more information about the image about the
가을 분포에 대한 이미지에 대해 더 많은 정보를 만들어
function of being implemented by this large ensemble ensemble is trying to
이 큰 앙상블 앙상블에 의해 구현되는 기능에 노력하고있다
head to bed soon do a really good job on giving you a probability probability
침대 머리는 곧 당신에게 확률 확률을주는 정말 좋은 일을
distribution over that image so then you can train the small model for normally
해당 이미지를 통해 배포 그래서 당신은 보통의 작은 모델을 학습 할 수 있습니다
when you train just training hard targets but instead you can train on
당신은 하드 목표를 교육 훈련 대신에 당신은에 훈련 할 때
some combination of the hard targets plus the soft targets and the training
하드 타겟 플러스 소프트 목표와 교육의 조합
objectives gonna try to Matt Matt should some function of those two things so
목표는 거 매트 매트 시도해야하는 두 가지 중 어떤 기능 때문에
this works surprisingly well so here's an experiment we did on a large speech
이것은 우리가 큰 연설에서했던 실험을 그래서 여기 놀라 울 정도로 잘 작동이다
model so we started by the model the classified 58.9 percent of his friends
모델은 그래서 우리는 모델에 따라 그의 친구의 분류 58.9 %로 시작
correctly that's our big accurate model and now we're going to use that horrible
제대로 그것은 우리의 큰 정확한 모델 그리고 지금 우리는 그 끔찍한를 사용하는거야
to provide soft targets for smaller model they also get to see the hard
작은 모델의 부드러운 목표를 제공하기 위해 그들은 또한 하드를 보게
target and we're gonna train that only 3% of the data so the new model with the
대상 및 우린 기차있어 그 데이터의 3 % 그래서 함께 새로운 모델
soft targets kept almost that accuracy 57% am just hard targets
부드러운 목표 정확도 57 %가 그냥 하드 목표입니다 거의 것을 유지
drastically over fits 44.5% accurate and then go south so soft targets are really
크게 이상 44.5 % 정확한 적합하고 매우 부드러운 목표는 정말 남쪽으로 이동
really good regularize and the other thing is that because the stock targets
정말 좋은 정례화하고, 다른 것은입니다 주식 목표 때문에
have so much information them compared to just a single one imagines arose you
너무 많은 정보들을 비교 한 단 하나의 하나의 상상 당신을 발생
train much much faster you get to that accuracy in like a week short about the
훈련을 훨씬 더 빨리 당신은에 대한 짧은 일주일 등에 그 정확성에 도착
time that that's pretty nice and you can do this approach with light drying
시간은 꽤 좋은 있다고 당신은 빛 건조에이 방법을 수행 할 수 있습니다
ensembles napping into one size model about ensemble you can do from a large
앙상블에 대한 하나의 크기 모델에 낮잠 앙상블 당신은 큰에서 수행 할 수 있습니다
bottle into a smaller one somewhat under-appreciated technique ok let's see
작은 일에 병 다소 과소 평가 기술은 확인 보자
so one of the things we did when we thought about building tons of flour was
그래서 우리가했던 것들 중 하나는 우리는 밀가루의 톤을 구축에 대해 생각했다 때
we kind of took a step back for more aware and we said what do you really
우리는 가지 더 알고 다시 단계를했고 우리가 정말 당신이 무엇을 말했다
want to research system so you want a lot of different things and it's kind of
당신이 다른 많은 것들을 할 수 있도록 시스템을 조회 할 그것을 가지의
hard to balance all of the things I but really one of the things you really care
당신이 정말로 관심있는 것들을 정말 한 일의 모든 I 그러나 하드 균형
about a few researcher is either the expression I wanna be able to take any
몇 연구원이 중 하나에 대해 내가 싶어 식은를 취할 수
old research idea and try it out
이전 연구 아이디어와 그것을 밖으로 시도
it was considerably smaller like instead of thousand wide fully connected layers
대신 천 폭 완전히 연결 계층 같은 상당히 작았
it was like 600 or 500 y which is actually a big difference but checking
그것은 600 실제로 큰 차이가 500 y를하지만 확인 같았다
that paper for the details I'm probably misremembered right and then you want to
자세한 것은 그 종이 아마 misremembered 권리를 해요 그리고 당신은 원하는
be able to take your research idea a lot and running quickly you want to be able
많은 당신이 할 수 있도록하려면 빨리 실행을 연구 아이디어를 취할 수
to run it probably on both data centers and iPhones nice to be able to reproduce
두 데이터 센터와 좋은 아이폰에 아마 그것을 실행하는 것은 재현 할 수 있도록
things and you want to go from a good research idea to a production system
일이 당신은 생산 시스템에 좋은 연구 아이디어에서 가고 싶어
without having to rewrite and some other system that's how we kind of the main
다시 및 다른 시스템 필요없이 그 방법을 우리 종류 주의의
things we were considering Wendling counterflow open source it as as you're
일이 우리는 당신이있어 등으로 역류 오​​픈 소스에게 그것을 웬들 링 고려했다
aware that our first emotion is flexible so the core bits of tender flow are we
첫 감정가요 유의 부드러운 유동의 코어 비트 우리 그래서
have a notion of different devices it is portable that runs on a much different
그것은 많은 다른 실행 휴대용 다른 장치의 개념이
operating systems we have this core graphics solution engine and then on top
운영 체제는 우리가 상단에 다음이 핵심 그래픽 솔루션 엔진과이
of that we have different friends were you expressed the kinds of competitions
그 중 우리는 다른 친구는 대회의 종류를 표현했다가
are trying to do we have a C++ friend and which most people don't use in my
수행하려는 우리는 C ++ 친구가 대부분의 사람들은에있는 사용하지 않는 내
mind we have the Piton friend I'm sure most of you are probably more so they
마음 우리는 당신의 확인 대부분은 더 그렇게 아마있는 밧줄 친구 야했다 그들은
don't have to wear most men but there's nothing preventing people from putting
대부분의 남자를 착용해야하지만 퍼팅에서 사람들을 방지 아무것도 없다하지 않습니다
other languages I wanted to be fairly language neutral so there is some work
몇 가지 작업이 때문에 다른 언어 나는 중립 상당히 언어가되고 싶어
going on to put ago friend on there
거기에 전 친구를 넣어 진행
other kinds of languages and you wanna be able to take that model and running
다른 언어의 종류 당신은 싶어 그 모델을 취할 수 및 실행해야
on a pretty wide variety of different platforms the basic computational model
다른 플랫폼의 매우 다양한 기본 계산 모델
is the ground I don't know how much talked about this in your overview of
나는 당신의 개요이 얘기 얼마나 모르는 땅이다
ten little bit ok so this graph things that flow along the edges or tenders for
열 좀 확인 가장자리 또는 입찰에 대한을 따라 흐름이 그래프 것들 때문에
arbitrary and dimensional arrays with a primitive type like Procter into unlike
달리으로 프록터와 같은 기본 유형으로 임의과 차원 배열
pure data flow models there's actually stayed in this crassly you have things
실제로이에 머물 것이 순수한 데이터 흐름 모델은 crassly 당신은 일이
like diocese which is a variable and then you have operations again update
교구와 같은 변수 후 다시 작업을 업데이트 한하는
things that happen system state can go through the whole graph compute some
전체 그래프는 몇 가지 계산을 통해 시스템 상태를 일 일이 갈 수 있습니다
gradient and then adjust the bias is based on gradient graph goes through a
구배 후 바이어스 조정은 기울기 그래프에 기초가 통과
series of stages one important stage is deciding given a whole bunch of
단계의 시리즈는 한 가지 중요한 단계는의 전체 무리를 주어 결정하는
computational devices and McGrath where are we in a run each of the different
실행에 서로 다른 각각의 우리를있는 연산 장치와 맥그래스
node in the graph terms of computation for example here we might have a CPU and
예를 들어 계산의 그래프 측면에서 노드가 여기에 우리가 CPU가있을 수 있습니다 및
blue and I GPU card and green and we might want to run the graph in such a
파란색과 I의 GPU 카드와 녹색과 우리는 같은에서 그래프를 실행할 수 있습니다
way that although that's a competition happens on the GPU so actually as an
방법이 그 경쟁이 정도로 실제로 GPU에서 발생 비록
aside this placement decisions are kind of tricky we allow users to provide him
옆이 배치 결정은 종류 우리는 사용자가 그에게 제공 할 수의 까다로운 있습니다
the guide this a bit and then given the hints which are not necessarily hard
가이드는이 비트와 반드시 하드없는 힌트가 주어
constraints on the new black device but might be something like you should
새로운 검은 장치에 있지만 제약은해야 같은 수 있습니다
really try to run this on a GPU or place it on task seven and I don't care what
정말 GPU에서이 작업을 실행하거나 작업 일곱에 배치하려고 난 상관 없어 무엇을
device and then we want to basically minimize the time for the graph subject
다음 장치 및 우리는 기본적 그래프 피사체 시간을 최소화 할
all kinds of other constraints like the memory we have available on each keep
우리가 서로에 사용할 수있는 메모리 같은 다른 제약 조건의 모든 종류의 유지
you Carter on CPUs I think it'd be interesting actually use at home at with
당신은 CPU에서 카터 나는 실제로와 집에서 사용하는 재미있을 거라고 생각
some reinforcement learning because you can actually measure an objective here
당신이 실제로 여기에 목표를 측정 할 수 있기 때문에 학습 일부 강화
of you know if I place this note and this known in this note in this way how
나는이 쪽지를 배치하면 당신을 알고이 이런 식으로 방법이 노트에 알려진
fast is my graph and I think that would be pretty interesting reinforcement
빨리 내 그래프이고, 나는 그것이 꽤 흥미 보강있을 거라고 생각
learning
배우기
problem 13 made decisions over to place things then we insert the sending
문제 13 우리는 전송을 삽입 한 후 물건을 배치하는 의사 결정을 통해 만든
receive nodes which essentially encapsulate all the communication system
기본적으로 모든 통신 시스템을 캡슐화 노드를받을
so basically you want to move it answer from one place to another the send nodal
그래서 기본적으로는 노드 전송이 한 장소에서 다른 답변을 이동하려면
kind of just hold onto the tensor until they receive no checks and they've
그들은 더 검사를받지 그들이 때까지 종류의 단지 텐서에 개최
really love that data for that and you do this for all the edges of the Cross
정말에 대한 데이터를 사랑하고 당신은 십자가의 모든 가장자리에 대해이 작업을 수행
device boundaries and you have different implications of sending receive Paris
장치 경계 및 수신 전송 파리의 다른 의미를 가지고
depending on the device see how for example if the GPUs are on the same
장치에 따라서 예를 들어, GPU는 동일한 방법에 있으면 볼
machine you can often do our DNA directly from one GPU memory to be there
기계 종종있을 하나의 GPU 메모리에서 직접 우리의 DNA를 수행 할 수 있습니다
if they're on different machines and you across machine RBC your network might
그들은 시스템에서 다른 시스템에있어, 당신이 경우 RBC 네트워크는 수도
support RDMA across the network and I case you would just use directly reach
그냥 직접 도달 할 때 사용하는 네트워크 및 I 케이스에서 지원 RDMA
into the southern GPU memory on the southern machine and credit you can
남부 기계와 당신이 할 수있는 신용의 남부 GPU 메모리에
define new operations and colonels pretty easily
아주 쉽게 새로운 운영 및 대령을 정의
such an interface is essentially how you run the graph can typically you run he
당신은 일반적으로 실행할 수있는 그래프를 실행하는 방법을 이러한 인터페이스는 그 본질적
set up a graph once and then you run a lot so that allows us to kind of have
한 번 그래프를 설정하고 우리가 가지 가질 수 있도록 당신은 많은 실행
the system do a lot of optimization and decisions about essentially how it wants
시스템은 원하는 본질적 방법에 대해 최적화 많은 의사 결정을 할
to place competition no then perhaps do some experiments on like does it make
그것을 만들 않는 등 몇 가지 실험을 할 아마도 더 후 경쟁을 배치 없습니다
more sense to put it here here because it's can advertise that overlap from
더 감각으로부터 중복을 광고 할 수 있습니다 여기 여기이기 때문에 그것을 넣어
author bryan calls the single process configuration everything runs and one
저자 브라이언은 단일 프로세스 구성 모든 실행 하나를 호출
process and it's just sort of simple procedure calls in a distributed setting
과정을 그리고 그것은 단지 종류의 간단한 절차는 분산 환경에서 호출이야
there's a client process a master process and then a bunch of workers that
노동자의 무리는이 클라이언트 프로세스는 마스터 프로세스이고 그
have devices and the Masterton clients as I'd like to run the subgraph the
나는 서브 그래프를 실행하려면 같은 장치와 마스터 톤의 클라이언트가
master says okay that means I need to talk to process wanted to tell them to
마스터는 내가 처리 할 얘기가에 그들에게 싶었 의미 괜찮 말한다
do stuff you can feed in fact data and that means that I might sort of have a
당신이 실제로 데이터에 공급할 수 물건을하고 그것이 내가 종류의를 가질 수 있음을 의미합니다
more complex graph but I only need to run little bits of it cause I only need
더 복잡한 그래프 그러나 나는 단지 내가 만하면 원인 그것의 작은 비트를 실행해야
to run the part to the computation that the output throughout our
계산에 대한 부분을 실행하는 내내 출력 우리의
are needed based on a story we focus a lot on being able to scale this
필요에 우리가 이것을 확장 할 수있는에 많은 초점 이야기를 기반으로
distributed environment we actually one of the biggest things when we first open
분산 환경 실제로 우리의 가장 큰 것 중 하나 때 우리가 처음 열려
source center for a week hadn't quite carved apart a open source mobile
일주일 동안 소스 센터는 꽤 오픈 소스 모바일 떨어져 조각하지 않았다
distributed implementation so that was good how this your number 23 which got
이 전화 번호 (23)를 가지고하는 방법 있도록 분산 구현은 좋았다
filed within like a day of our release that hey where's the distributed version
헤이 분산 버전의 우리의 릴리스의 일처럼 이내에 제출
we did the initial released last Thursday so that's good it'll get better
그게거야 더 좋은, 그래서 우리는 처음 출시 된 지난 목요일했다
packaging but at the moment you can kind of and configure multiple processes with
포장하지만 순간에 당신의 종류 및 여러 프로세스를 구성 할 수 있습니다
the names of the other process he's involved IP addresses importance we're
다른 프로세스의 이름 그는 우리가있어 관련 IP 주소의 중요성입니다
gonna package that I'm better and next couple of weeks but that's good and the
내가 주 더 앞으로 몇이야하지만 그건 좋은 및 거 패키지
whole reason to have that is that you want much better turnaround time for
그것을 가지고 온 이유는 훨씬 더 나은 처리 시간을 할 것입니다
experiments so if you're in the mode where your training and experiment
실험은 모드 훈련 및 실험에 있다면 그렇게
iteration is kind of minutes or hours that's really really good if you're in
반복 당신이 있다면 정말 정말 좋은 분 또는 몇 시간의 종류
the mode of like multiple weeks that's kind of hopeless like more than a month
한 달보다 종류의 희망처럼 더 같은 여러 주 모드
you you generally want to do it or if you do you're like oh my travels done
당신이 당신은 일반적으로 작업을 수행 할 또는 당신이 할 경우, 당신은 할 나의 여행 오 ​​같은거야
why did I do that again so we really emphasize a lot in our group just being
왜 우리가 정말 우리 그룹에서 많이 강조 다시 그래서 그냥되는 것이 했는가
able to make it to people can do experiments as fast as is reasonable
합리적으로 빨리 실험을 할 수있는 사람을 만들 수
so the two main things we do our model parallels amid a problem I'll talk about
그래서 두 가지 일이 우리는 내가 대해 얘기하자 문제 속에서 우리의 모델 평행선을
both you've talked about this a little bit or ok so the best way you can
모두 당신이 조금 또는 확인이 이야기 한 당신이 할 수있는 가장 좋은 방법은 이렇게
decrease 9 training time is decreased to stop time so one of the really nice
(9) 교육 시간을 단축하는 것은 그래서 정말 좋은 중 하나를 시간을 중지 감소
properties most laptops there's lots and lots of inherent parallelism right like
속성 대부분의 노트북을 많이하고 고유의 병렬 권리 등 많이있다
if you think about a computational model there's lots of parallelism
당신이 계산 모델에 대해 생각하면 병렬 많이있다
each of the layers because all the spatial positions are mostly independent
각 층의 모든 공간 위치는 거의 무관하므로
you can just run around them
당신은 단지 그들 주위에 실행할 수 있습니다
in parallel on different devices the problem is figure out how to communicate
다른 장치에 병렬로 문제가 통신하는 방법을 알아낼 수있다
how to distribute that computation in such a way that doesn't kill you if you
같은 방법으로 그 계산을 배포하는 것은 당신을 경우 죽이지 않는 방법
think help you someone is local conductivity like convolutional neural
도움이 사람이 길쌈 신경 같은 지역의 전도성 당신 생각
mats have this nice property that they're generally looking like a five by
매트는 일반적으로 오에 의해처럼 찾고이 좋은 특성을 가지고
five patch of data below them and they don't need anything else and the neuron
오 그 아래의 데이터를 패치하고 다른 아무것도 신경 세포가 필요하지 않습니다
next to it as a whole lot of overlap with the data it needs for for that
그것은 그것을 위해에 필요한 데이터와 중복 훨씬로서 그 옆에
first neuron UCAV towers with little or no connectivity between the towers so
타워 사이 거의 또는 전혀 연결을 통해 먼저 신경 UCAV 타워 그래서
every few layers you might communicate a little bit but mostly you don't accept
마다 몇 층 당신은 약간의 의사 소통 수도 있지만 대부분은 당신이 동의하지 않습니다
paper did that so essentially had two separate hours that mostly ran into
종이 그래서 기본적으로 대부분 우연히 두 개의 별도의 시간을 한 것으로 한
penalty on GPUs to different CPUs and occasionally exchanged some information
다른 CPU에 GPU가와에 대한 처벌은 때때로 몇 가지 정보를 교환
you get a specialized parts of the model attractive woman for some example
당신은 몇 가지 예를 들어 모델 매력적인 여자의 전문 부품을 얻을
there's lots of ways to exploit parallelism so when you're just naively
당신은 그냥 순진하게있을 때 그래서 병렬을 악용 할 수있는 방법이 많이있다
compiling matrix multiply code with gcc or something it a lot probably already
아마 이미 GCC 또는 무언가 그 많은 행렬 곱셈 코드를 컴파일
take advantage of instruction parallelism present on Intel CPUs scores
인텔의 CPU 점수에 명령 병렬 선물을 활용
you can use Thread heroism and things that way across devices communicating
당신은 통신 기기에서 스레드 영웅주의와 가지 방법을 사용할 수 있습니다
between the abusers often pretty limited to you have like a factor of 30 to 40
종종 꽤 당신에게 한정 학대자 사이에 30 ~ 40 배처럼이
better band trip to the local team member you can you do to like another
로컬 팀 구성원에 더 밴드 여행 당신은 다른 좋아 할 수있는
GPU cards memory on the same machine and across machine down in general even
동일한 시스템에서 GPU 카드 메모리와 시스템에서 일반적으로 아래도
worse so pretty important to kind of keep as much data local as you can and
더 나쁜 종류의 당신이 할 수있는 지역의 많은 데이터를 유지하기 때문에 매우 중요하고
avoid eating too much but model parallels in the basic idea is you're
당신이있어입니다 기본 개념에 너무 많이하지만 모델 평행선을 먹고 피
just going to partition the computational model somehow maybe
그냥 어떻게 든 아마 계산 모델을 분할하는 것
especially like this maybe layer by layer and then in this case for example
특히 층으로하고, 예를 들어이 경우이 어쩌면 층 등
the only communication I need to do is that this boundary you know some of the
내가해야 할 유일한 통신이 경계 당신이 몇몇을 알고있다
data from petition to have needed for the input of that partition one but
청원의 데이터가 해당 파티션의 입력에 필요한 가지고 일하지만,
mostly all that is local the other techniques you can use for speeding up
대부분 모든 당신이 속도에 사용할 수있는 다른 기술 지역입니다
convergence is data parallelism some a case you're going to use many different
컨버전스는 일부 데이터 병렬 처리가 다른 많은 사용하려고하는 경우입니다
replicas of the same model structure and they're all going to collaborate to
동일 모델 구조의 복제본 그들은 모든 협력거야
update parameters so in some shared set of servers that hold the parameters
매개 변수를 잡고 일부는 서버의 공유 세트에 있도록 업데이트 매개 변수
state speedups depend a lot on the kind of model could be 10 to 40 X speed up
상태 속도 향상은 속도 모델의 종류에 많은 10-40 X이 될 수 의존
450 replicas sparse models with like really large embeddings for every
모든에 대해 같은 정말 큰 묻어 450 복제본 스파 스 모델을
vocabulary word known to man
인간에게 알려진 어휘 단어
generally you can't report more parallelism cuz most updates only update
대부분의 업데이트는 업데이트 사촌 일반적으로 더 많은 병렬 처리를보고 할 수 없습니다
a handful of the embedding entries have a sentence has like 10 unique words in
매립 항목의 소수 문장은 10와 같은 독특한 단어를 가지고 있습니다
it out of a million and you can have millions and millions are thousands of
만 밖으로 당신은 수백만을 가질 수 있고, 수백만의 수천
replicas doing lots of work so the basic idea and data parallelism is you have
기본 개념 및 데이터 병렬 처리는 당신이 그래서 일을 많이하고 복제본
these different model replicas are gonna have the centralized system that keeps
서로 다른 모델 복제본 유지하는 중앙 집중식 시스템을 거 가지고있다
track of the parameters that may not just be a single machine and maybe a lot
단지 하나의 기계와 아마 많이하지 않을 수 있습니다 매개 변수 추적
of machines because you need a lot of network bandwidth sometimes to keep all
기계의 당신은 때로는 모든 유지하기 위해 네트워크 대역폭을 많이 필요로하기 때문에
these model replica standard parameters so that might you know in our big setup
그래서이 모델 복제 표준 매개 변수 당신은 우리의 큰 설정에서 알 수 있습니다
that my behind and 27 machines been stopped and then you know you might have
내 뒤에 (27) 기계 후 중지 된 것을 당신은 당신이있을 수 있습니다 알고
five and replicas of the models down there and before every model replica
다섯 거기 모델의 복제본과 모든 모델 복제하기 전에
doesn't match its gonna grab the parameters so it says okay you hundred
그것은 당신에게 백을 좋아 말한다, 그래서 그거야 매개 변수를 잡아 일치하지 않습니다
and twenty-seven machines give me the parameters and then it does a
및 스물일곱 기계는 나에게 매개 변수를 제공 한 후는 않습니다
combination of around the mini badge and because I would agree it should be it
미니 배지 주변의 조합 동의 것이기 때문에 그것을해야한다
doesn't apply to rate of time degrading back to the parameters servers routers
매개 변수 서버 라우터로 다시 분해 시간의 속도에 적용되지 않습니다
servers then update the current parameter values and then before the
서버는 그 후 이전에 현재의 매개 변수 값을 업데이트
next step we did the same thing really network intensive depending on your
다음 단계 우리는 같은 일이 정말로 집중에 따라 네트워크했다 당신의
model things that help here are modeled the don't have very many parameters
(가) 매우 많은 매개 변수가없는 여기에 도움이 모델로있는 모델 일
competitions are really nice in that respect Ella standardise in that respect
대회는 그 점 엘라는 그런 점에서 표준화 정말 멋지다
because you're essentially than reusing every parameter lock them up the time so
당신은 재사용보다 본질적이기 때문에 모든 매개 변수는 너무 시간을 잠글
you're already using you know however bigger batch size is on the model of
당신은 이미 당신은 그러나 더 큰 배치 크기를 알고 사용하는 것은의 모델에
your child's 228 you're gonna bring pressure over you can use a hundred and
당신이 백을 사용할 수 있습니다 통해 자녀의 228는 거 압력을 가지고있어와
twenty eight times for all the columns in the match but have a convolutional
경기의 모든 열에 대한 스물여덟 시간 만은 길쌈을
model now you're gonna get an additional factor of reuse of maybe like $10 in
모델은 지금 넌 아마 같은 $ 10 재사용의 추가 팩터를 얻을 수있어
different positions
다른 위치
in a layer that you're going to use it an analysis p.m. if you unroll a hundred
층에 당신은 당신이 백을 풀다 경우를 분석 오후를 사용하는 거라고
times steps you can reuse it a hundred times just for the unrolling those kinds
시간은 그냥 그 종류를 줄이기 위해 그것을 백 번을 다시 사용할 수 있습니다 단계
of things that have model have lots of computation and fewer parameters to sort
모델이 물건의 정렬 계산을 많이 적은 매개 변수가
of Dr that competition generally will work better and did a parallel
박사의 경쟁은 일반적으로 잘 작동과 평행 한 것
environments now there's an obvious issue depending on how you do those so
환경은 지금 당신이 그렇게 그 작업을 수행하는 방법에 따라 명백한 문제가있다
one way you can do this is completely asynchronously every model replicas just
당신이 할 수있는 한 가지 방법은 완전하게 비동기 적으로 모든 모델 복제본입니다
sitting in a loop and setting the parameters doing a mini badge heating
미니 배지 난방을하는 루프에 앉아 매개 변수를 설정
radiant sending it up there and if you do that asynchronously then the gradient
복사가 그것을 보내고 당신은 비동기 적으로 다음 그라데이션을 그렇게 할 경우
computes may be completely stale with respect to the where the parameters are
계산하여이 매개 변수는 곳에 대해 완전히 부패 할 수있다
now right now is computed it with his back to this parameter value but
지금 현재이 매개 변수 값에 자신의 뒤쪽에 그것을 계산하지만,
meanwhile 10 other applicants have made called the parameters to meander over
한편 10 다른 지원자가 만든은을 통해 사행하는 매개 변수를 호출
here and now you apply the gradient that you thought was for here this makes the
여기 그리고 지금 당신은 당신이이 만드는 여기에 대한라고 생각 그라데이션을 적용
additions incredibly uncomfortable there already uncomfortable cuz it's
그것의 사촌 이미 불편이 추가 매우 불편
completely non conduct problems but the good news is it worked up to a certain
완전히 비 윤리 문제 그러나 좋은 소식은 그것이 어떤까지 일
level it would be really good understand the conditions under which you know this
수준 당신이 알고있는 조건을 이해 정말 좋은 것
works and theoretical basis but in practice it does seem to work pretty
작품과 이론적 기초하지만, 실제로는 꽤 작동하도록 보인다
well the other thing you can do is do this completely synchronously so you can
잘 당신이 할 수있는 다른 일이 완전히 동 기적으로 당신이 할 수있는 그래서 이렇게이다
have one driving loop that sounds ok everyone go they all get the parameters
확인 모든 사람들이 그들 모두가 매개 변수를 가서 소리 하나 운전 루프가
they all compute gradients and then you wait for the gradients to show up and do
그들은 모두 계산 그라디언트 다음은 그라데이션을 기다리는는 표시와해야 할 일
something with a great effort to them around her and that effectively just
그녀의 주위에 그들에게 큰 노력 뭔가하고 효과적으로 단지
looks like a giant batch are replicas that looks like you know our times each
거대한 일괄처럼 보인다는 당신이 우리의 회를 알고처럼 보이는 그 복제본
individual ones batch size which sometimes works you kind of get
때때로 당신이 가지 얻을 작동 개개의 일괄 처리 크기
diminishing returns from larger and larger batch sizes but the more training
더 큰 배치 크기 만 더 훈련에서 수익을 감소
examples you have
예 당신이
more tolerant you are a bigger bite sized generally have a trillion training
더 관대 한 당신은 더 큰 바이트는 일반적으로 크기 조 훈련을하다
examples you know about the size of a thousand ok you have a million training
당신이 천 확인의 크기에 대해 알고 예는 백만 훈련을
examples outside of a thousand not so great right
천 그리 좋은하지 못 외부의 예
think I said Lewis there's even more complicated choices are you can have
내가 훨씬 더 복잡한 선택은 당신이 할 수 있습니다 거기에 루이스했다 생각
like a descriptive ends in Europe right I said that the current models are good
유럽​​의 권리를 설명 끝처럼 현재의 모델은 좋은했다
they reuse the parameters a lot so data parallelism is actually really really
데이터 병렬 정말 정말 실제로 그래서 그들은 매개 변수를 많이 재사용
important for almost all of our models that's how we get to the point of
우리의 모델의 거의 모든 중요한 그것은 우리가 지점에 도착 방법
training models in like half a day or a day generally so you know you see some
같은 반에서 교육 모델은 하루 일반적으로 하루 그래서 당신은 당신이 어떤 참조 알고
of the rough kind of setup for use and here's an example training graph of
사용 설정의 거친 종류의 이곳은의 예 훈련 그래프이다
image net model one GPU 10 GB used 52 views and there's the kind of speed up
이미지 네트 모델 하나의 GPU 10기가바이트 52 뷰를 사용하고 최대 속도의 종류가있다
yet
아직
like sometimes these graphs are receiving like the difference between 10
같은 때때로 이러한 그래프는 10의 차이처럼 받고있다
and 50 years doesn't seem that big like lines are kind of close to each other
50 년 라인과 같은 큰 각 다른 종류의 가까운 것을하지 않는 것
soldiers but in actual fact the difference between 10 and 50 is like a
군인하지만 실제 사실 10과 50의 차이는 같다
factor of four point want something so that doesn't look like a factor 4.1
그 요인 4.1처럼 보이지 않도록 네 점의 요인은 무엇인가를 원하는
difference does it but it is yeah the way you do it as you would like without
차이를 수행하지만, 그래 당신이없이 원하는만큼 당신이 그것을 할 방법입니다
one crisis point six and seven thousand crisis point ok
하나의 위기 지점 여섯 칠천 위기 지점 확인
so let me show you some of the slight tweaks you make to tender for models to
그래서 내가 당신에게 당신이에 모델에 입찰 할 수 있도록 약간의 개조하면 되겠 어의 일부를 보여 드리겠습니다
exploit these different kinds of parallelism one of the things we wanted
병렬 처리의 서로 다른 종류의 악용 우리가 원하는 것들 중 하나
was for these kinds of parallelism notions to be pretty easy to express so
병렬 개념의 이러한 종류이었다 그렇게 표현 꽤 쉽게하기
one of the things I like about 20 mins it maps pretty well to the kind of
것들 중 하나는 난의 종류에 꽤 잘 매핑 약 20 분을 좋아한다
things you might see in a research paper so it's not talk to read all that but
이 얘기 아니에요 있도록 연구 논문에서 볼 수있는 일이 읽을 수있는 모든 것을하지만,
it's not too different than what you would see you should never be kinda nice
당신은 당신이 좀 좋은되어서는 안 볼 것입니다 무엇보다 너무 다른 아니에요
like a simple stem cell this is the sequence to sequence model that only a
간단한 줄기 세포처럼이 시퀀스 모델에 순서입니다 만
subsidiary organ all the quickly published in its 2014 we're essentially
보조 기관이 신속하게 2014 년에 출판 된 모든 우리는 본질적으로있어
trying to take an input sequence and map it turned out that sequence this is a
입력 시퀀스를 가지고 매핑하는 시도는 이것이하다 서열을 밝혀
really big area of research it turns out these kinds of models are applicable for
연구의 정말 큰 영역은 모델 이러한 종류의에 적용 할 수 있습니다 밝혀
lots and lots of kinds of problems there's lots of different groups doing
문제의 종류를 많이하고 많이 다른 그룹 많이하고있다
interesting inactive work in this area so here's just some examples of recent
그래서 여기에이 지역에서 흥미로운 비활성 작업은 최근의 단지 몇 가지 예입니다
work in the last year and a half in this area from what the different labs around
어떤 다른 실험실 주변에서이 지역의 마지막 년 반에서 일
the world you've already talked about it
당신이 이미 그것에 대해 얘기했습니다 세계
caption call just so instead of a sequence you can put in pixels are you
당신은 픽셀 단위로 넣을 수 있습니다 그냥 대신 시퀀스의 자막 호출은 당신입니다
put in pixels you went through CNN that's your initial state and then you
당신은 당신의 초기 상태의 당신이 CNN을 통해 갔다 픽셀에 넣고
can generate captions pretty amazing
꽤 놀라운 캡션을 생성 할 수 있습니다
35 years ago contributor to that I was I don't think so not for a while Harry R
삼십오년 전 나는 잠시 동안 해리 R에 대해 그렇게하지를 생각하지 않는에 기여했다
you can actually do and then I say it's a generative model so you can generate
당신은 실제로 할 수있는 다음 당신이 생성 할 수 있도록이 생식 모델 말할
different sentences by exploring the distribution you know I think both of us
분포를 탐구하여 다른 문장은 내가 우리 모두를 생각하는지
are not captains it's not quite a sophisticated of the human one don't
선장은 인간 하나의 매우 정교한가 안하지 않은 것은하지 않습니다
often see this one of the things is
종종 사물의 하나입니다 참조
if you if you train the model little bit it's really important to her trainer
당신이 모델 조금 훈련하면 경우는 그녀의 트레이너 정말 중요합니다
model to convergence because light that's not so bad but if you train that
그렇게 나쁘지 않아 빛이 있기 때문에 모델이 수렴하지만 당신은 것을 훈련하는 경우
model longer the same model just got a lot better
모델 이상 같은 모델은 훨씬 더있어
same thing here right training that is sitting on the tracks yes that's true
트랙에 앉​​아있다 여기에 같은 일을 바로 훈련은 예 그건 사실이야
but that ones better but she still see the human has a lot more sophistication
하지만 사람이 더 나은하지만 그녀는 여전히 볼 수있는 사람은 훨씬 더 세련가
right like they know that they're crossed the tracks near a depot that's
그들은의 저장소 근처에 트랙을 교차하고 있음을 알 권리처럼
sort of a more subtle thing that the model to pick up on another kind of cute
모델이 귀여운 다른 종류의에 데리러 것을 더 미묘한 물건의 종류
using you can actually use them to solve all kinds of cool graph problems so or
을 사용하여 실제로 매우 시원 그래프 모든 종류의 문제를 해결하는 데 사용할 수 있거나
even yalls mara Fortunato and FTP this work which you start with a ton of
도 마라 포르투나 및 FTP 당신의 톤으로 시작이 일을 yalls
points and then you try to predict the traveling salesman for that works best
포인트는 그게 잘 작동에 대한 외판원을 예측하려고
for the convex hull or Delonte triangulation of grass gonna call you
잔디의 볼록 선체 또는 Delonte 삼각 측량을위한거야 전화
know it's just a secret the sequence problem for you feat in the sequence of
그것은 단지의 순서에 당신 위업에 대한 시퀀스 문제 비밀 알고
points and then the output is the right set of points for whatever problem you
점하고 출력은 어떤 문제에 대한 포인트의 설정 오른쪽은 당신
care about
에 대한 관심
reply ok so I'll scams so once you have that Alice p.m. cellco that I showed you
내가 사기를거야, 그래서 당신이 한 번, 그래서 확인 응답이 내가 당신을 보여 앨리스 오후 cellco
on there you can enroll in time twenty time steps let's say you wanted four
거기에 당신의 당신이 네 가지를 원 가정 해 봅시다 시간 스무 시간 단계에 등록 할 수 있습니다
layers per time step instead of one
시간 단계 당 층 대신 하나
well you would make a little bit of change your code and you do that now you
잘 당신은 당신의 코드를 변경의 약간을 만들 것입니다 그리고 당신은 지금 그렇게
have four layers of computations 2011 of the things you might want to do is run
계산의 4 층 당신이 할 수있는 일의 2011 실행이
each of those layers on a different GPU so that's the change would make you tons
그래서 다른 GPU에 그 층의 각각의 변화가 톤을 만들 것입니다
of occurred to do that and that allows you to have a model like this so this is
의 작업을 수행 발생하고 당신이 그래서 이런 모델을 할 수 있습니다
my sequins these are the different deep jealousy I'm layers I have per time step
내 장식 조각이 나는 시간 단계 당이 난 층이야 다른 깊은 질투하다
and after the first little bit I can start getting more and more GPUs kind of
첫 번째 조금 후 나는 점점 더 많은 GPU를을 가지지고 시작할 수 있습니다
involved in the process
과정에 관여
and you essentially pipeline the entire thing there's a giant soft packs at the
당신은 기본적으로 파이프 라인 전체 것은 상기 거대한 소프트 팩있다
top of you can split across keep you pretty easily do that to model
당신의 상단은 아주 쉽게 모델에 그렇게 유지에 걸쳐 분할 할 수 있습니다
parallelism right we've now got six GPUs in this picture we actually use a split
병렬 바로 우리가 지금이 사진을 우리가 실제로 분할을 사용하여 여섯 GPU가있어
that soft max cross-border abuses and man it so every replica would be a GPU
그 부드러운 최대 국경을 남용하고 남자는 그렇게 모든 복제본은 GPU 것
cards on the same machine all kind of humming along and then you might use
동일한 시스템에서 카드를 따라 흥얼의 모든 종류 그리고 당신은 사용할 수 있습니다
data parallelism in addition to that
그 외에도, 데이터 병렬성
to train a bunch of AGP card replicas to train quickly we have this notion of QS
빨리 훈련하는 AGP 카드 복제의 무리를 양성하는 우리는 QS의이 개념이
he can kind of have her photographs the do a bunch of stuff and then suffered an
그는 종류의 그녀가 잔뜩 할 사진이 한 다음 고통을 수 있습니다
EQ and then later you have another bit of time to photograph that starts with D
다음 EQ와 나중에는 D로 시작 사진과 시간의 또 다른 비트가
hearings and stuff and then a dozen things so one and one example is you
청문회 물건 후 십여 가지 하나 하나의 예는 그래서
might want to prefetch inputs and then why do the JPEG decoding to convert them
변환하는 JPEG 디코딩을 할 이유를 다음 입력을 프리 페치와 할 수 있습니다
into sort of arrays and maybe do some whitening and cropping a random
배열의 종류에 어쩌면 약간의 미백을하고 임의 자르기
selection of men's stuff like you and then you can then dq on a different GPU
당신 같은 사람의 물건을 선택하고 당신은 다른 GPU에 DQ 수 있습니다
cards or something we also can group similar examples for translation work we
카드 또는 뭔가 우리 또한 할 수있는 번역 작업의 우리에 대한 그룹 유사한 예
actually bucket by length of sentence so that your batch has a bunch of examples
당신의 배치 예에 무리가되도록 실제로 문장의 길이에 의해 버킷
that are all roughly the same sentence length all 13 216 words sentences or
그 모두 거의 같은 문장 길이 모두 13 216 단어 문장
something that just means we even need only execute exactly that many unrolled
단지 우리가 심지어해야 만 정확하게 많은 펼쳐진 실행 의미 일
steps rather than you know arbitrary next sentence length good for
당신이 임의의 다음 문장 길이 잘 알고보다는 단계
randomization challenged members shuffling cue is just a whole bunch of
임의 회원 큐는 단지 전체 무리입니다 셔플 도전
examples and then get random ones out
예를 들면 다음 밖으로 임의의 사람을 얻을
data parallelism right so again we want to be able to have many replicas of this
데이터 병렬 바로 그래서 다시 우리는이 많은 복제본을 가질 수 있도록하려면
thing and so you make a modest amount of changes to your we're not quite as happy
것은 그래서 당신은 우리있어 꽤 행복하지 않은 변경의 적당한 양을
with this amount of change but this is kind of what you do there's a supervisor
하지만 변화의 양이 감독자가 무엇 당신이 할의 종류
that has a bunch of things you now say there's pressure devices and prepare the
그것은 당신이 지금 압력 장치가 말할와 준비 사물의 무리가
session and then each one of these rounds a local loop and you not keep
세션 후 다음 라운드의 각 로컬 루프 당신은 유지하지
track of how many steps have been applied globally across all the
얼마나 많은 단계의 트랙 모두에 걸쳐 전 세계적으로 적용되었습니다
different replicas and soon is the cumulative sum of all those is big
곧 다른 복제본과 모든 사람들의 누적 합계가 큰입니다
enough for a synchronous training looks kinda like that three separate client
동기 훈련을 위해 충분히 그 세 가지 별도의 클라이언트처럼 ​​좀 보인다
dreads driving three separate replicas all with parameters so one of the big
그래서 모든 매개 변수와 함께 큰 중 하나를 세 가지 별도의 복제본을 구동 두려워
implications from disbelief to tend to flow if we don't have the separate
우리는 분리가없는 경우 불신에서 의미가 흐르는 경향하기
parameters server notion we have answers and variables variables that contained
매개 변수 서버 개념 우리가 포함 된 답변 변수 변수를
answers and they're just other parts of the graph and typically you map them
답변 그들은 그래프의 단지 다른 부분이고 일반적으로 당신이 그들을지도
onto a small set of devices they're gonna hold you parameters but it's all
장치의 작은 세트에 그들은 당신에게 매개 변수를 거 보유하고 있지만 전부
kind of unified in the same framework whether I'm sending it to answer that
나는 그 대답을 보낸다 여부 종류의 같은 프레임 워크에 통합
parameters or activations or whatever doesn't matter this is kind of a
매개 변수 또는 정품 인증 또는이 문제가되지 않습니다 어떤이의 종류
synchronous do you have one client and I just split my batch across three
동기는 하나의 클라이언트를 가지고 난 그냥 세에서 내 배치를 분할 할
replicas and had the gradient and apply them know might turn out to be pretty
복제 기울기를 가지고 있었고, 꽤 것으로 판명 수 있습니다 알고 적용하고
tolerant of reduced precision so convert to FB 16 there's actually and I Tripoli
감소 정밀도의 허용 그렇게 FB (16)가 실제로 있고 난 트리폴리 변환
standard for 16 to 14 points now putting point I use now most CPU don't quite
16 ~ 14 점은 현재 지점을두고 표준 내가 할 지금 대부분의 CPU 사용하지 꽤
support that yet so we implemented our own sixteen-bit format which is
아직 우리가 우리 자신의 여섯 비트 형식을 구현 지원
essentially we have a 32 bit floating be lopped off to buy to me
기본적으로 우리는 32 비트 부동는 나에게 구입 잘려 수있다
and you should kind of new stochastic public but we don't so sort of ok it's
당신은 종류의 확률 공공 새로운하지만 우리가 종류의 확인은 안해야
just know if any concurred converted to 32 bit on the other side by filling in
어떤에서 작성하여 다른 측면에서 32 비트 변환 동의하면 바로 알
for it it's very sleepy roof friendly paper while still model and data
그것을 위해 여전히 모델링 및 데이터하면서 매우 졸린 지붕 친화적 인 종이입니다
parallelism in conjunction bind really likes you train models quickly and
함께 바인딩에서 병렬 정말 빠르게 모델을 훈련 좋아
that's what this is all really about is being able to take a research idea try
즉,이 모든 정말로에 대한 시도 연구 아이디어를 가지고 할 수있는입니다 무엇
it out on a large dataset is representative of a problem you care
큰 데이터 세트에 그것을 밖으로는 상관 문제의 대표
about
약
figure out that work figure out the next set of experiments as it's pretty easy
꽤 쉽게로 실험의 다음 세트 밖으로 그 일의 숫자를 파악
to express intensive load the data profile somewhere not too happy with for
어딘가에 집중 하중을위한 너무 행복하지 않은 데이터 프로파일을 표현하는
a synchronous parallelism but in general it's not too bad we have open source
동기 병렬 처리는 일반적으로 우리가 오픈 소스가 너무 나쁜 아니지만
center flow because we think that'll make it easier to share research writing
센터 흐름을 우리가보다 쉽게​​ 연구 기록을 공유 할 수있을 거라 생각하기 때문에
is we think you know having lots of people using the system outside of
우리는 당신이 외부 시스템을 사용하는 많은 사람들을 가지는 알고 생각입니다
Google was there is a good thing to improve it and bring ideas that we don't
구글을 개선하고 우리가하지 않는 아이디어를 가져 오는 좋은 일이 있었다
necessarily how it makes it pretty easy to deploy machine learning systems into
반드시이에 기계 학습 시스템을 구축하는 것이 매우 쉽게하는 방법
real products because you can go from our research idea into something running
실제 제품은 당신이 뭔가를 실행에 우리의 연구 아이디어에서 갈 수 있기 때문에
on a phone relatively easily the community of tens of users outside
상대적으로 쉽게 전화 외부 수십 사용자의 커뮤니티
Google is growing which is nice how they're doing all kinds of cool things I
구글은 멋진 사물의 모든 종류의 일을하는 방법 좋은 인 성장 I
picked a few random examples of things people have done that are posted and get
고른 게시 얻을 사람들이 수행 한 일의 몇 가지 임의의 예
how this is one that's like Andre has this discontent at Daylesford runs in
이 안드레처럼 하나의 방법 데일 스 포드가에서 실행에서이 불만을 가지고
your browser using javascript and one of the things he has a little game he's
브라우저를 사용하여 자바 스크립트와 그가 약간 게임의 한 것들 중 하나
reinforcement learning the yellow dot learns to get learns to eat the real
노란색 점을 학습 보강 배운다 진짜 먹고 얻을 수 배운다
urgency the Green Dot to avoid the red dots so someone reimplemented that in
긴급 녹색 점은 누군가에 그것을 다시 구현하도록 빨간색 점을 피하기 위해
terms of flow and actually added orange dots are really bad
흐름의 관점 실제로 추가 오렌지 도트 정말 나쁜
someone implemented this really nice paper from University of Tilburg in the
누군가가에 틸 부르 흐 대학에서이 정말 좋은 종이를 구현
Max Planck Institute only be seen this work are you take an image a picture and
막스 플랑크 연구소는 당신이 사진 이미지를 촬영하는이 작품을 볼 수과
typically a painting and then renders that picture in the style of that paper
일반적으로 다음 그림과 해당 용지의 스타일에서 해당 사진을 렌더링
and you end up with the cool stuff like that bad you know there's a character
당신은 당신이 문자가 알고 나쁜처럼 멋진 물건으로 끝날
and model here outside the popular sort of higher-level library to make it
높은 수준의 라이브러리의 인기 정렬 외부 여기 모델을 만드는
easier to express mail mats someone implemented the neural captioning model
쉽게 메일 매트를 표현하는 사람이 신경 자막 모델을 구현
in terms of low there's our effort underway to translated into Mandarin
중국어로 번역에 낮은 측면에서 우리의 노력이 진행되고있다
cool great last thing I will talk about the brain residency programs we've
멋진 위대한 마지막 것은 우리가했습니다 뇌 레지던시 프로그램에 대해 이야기합니다
started this program a bit of an experiment this year and so this is more
실험의 비트 올해이 프로그램을 시작하고 그래서 이것은 더
as an FYI for next year cause or applications are closed rectory
참고로 내년 원인 또는 응용 프로그램에 대한 폐쇄 사제관으로
selecting our final candidates this week and then the idea is the people will
사람들은 것 이번 주에 우리의 최종 후보를 선택한 다음 생각은
spend a year in our group doing deep learning research and the hope is
깊은 학습 연구를하고 우리 그룹의 올해 투자 및 희망이다
they'll come out and have published a couple of papers on archiver submitted
그들은 나올 것입니다 및 제출 아카이버 논문의 몇 가지를 발표했다
to Companies is and learn a lot about doing sort of interesting machine
회사에하고 흥미로운 기계의 종류를하는 것에 대해 많은 것을 배울
learning research and now we're looking for people for next year obviously about
연구를 배우고 지금 우리에 대해 분명히 내년 사람을 찾고있어
our strong in you know anyone taking the class will reopen applications in the
당신은 애플리케이션을 다시 할 수업을 아는 사람에 우리의 강한
fall
가을
graduating like next year opportunity there you go there's a bunch more
내년에 기회처럼 졸업 거기 당신은 무리가 더있어 이동
reading there
이 읽기
start your cuz I did a lot of work in the white paper to make the whole set of
당신의 사촌을 시작 난의 전체 세트를 만들기 위해 흰 종이에 많은 일을했다
references clickable and then click your way through 250 other figures ok so I
참조를 클릭 한 다음 확인을 그래서 250 다른 인물을 통해 귀하의 방법을 클릭합니다 I
have been done early
초기에 수행 된
hundred and sixty-five
백 육십 오
yes so those kind of things are actually tricky and we have an actually a pretty
예 그래서 사물의 그 종류는 실제로 까다로운 그리고 우리는 실제로 꽤있다
extensive detailed process for things that are you know talking about you're
당신이 당신에 대해 얘기를 알고있는 것 것들에 대한 광범위한 세부 과정
using a user's private data for these kinds of things so smart reply
일 똑똑 응답 이러한 종류의 사용자의 개인 정보를 사용
essentially all the replies that word that it ever will generate are things
이제까지 생성됩니다 기본적으로 모든 응답이 단어는 것들
that have been said by thousands of users so the input to the model for
수천 명의 사용자로 말했다되었습니다 있도록하기위한 모델에 입력
training is an email which is typically not about how the people at but the only
교육 방법에 대해 사람들하지만 단지에 대해 일반적으로하지 않은 이메일입니다
things will ever suggest are things that are generated in response by you know
지금까지 제안합니다 일이 당신이 알고에 의해 응답으로 생성되는 것들
suspicion number of unique users to protect the privacy of users that put
고유 한 사용자의 의심 번호를 넣어 사용자의 개인 정보를 보호하기 위해
kind of things you're thinking about when designing products like cotton and
면 같은 제품을 설계 할 때 약 당신이 생각하는 물건의 종류
is actually a lot of Karen thought going into you know we think this will be a
실제로 카렌의 많은 당신에 갈 생각된다 우리가이가 될 것이라고 생각을 알고
great feature but how can we do this in a way that ensures the people's privacy
훌륭한 기능 그러나 우리는 사람들의 프라이버시를 보장하는 방식으로이 작업을 수행 할 수있는 방법
is protected
보호
as much as we probably should have assured it's just kind of been one of
우리는 아마 그것을 보장해야하는만큼 그냥 가지 중 하나가되었습니다
the things on the back burner compared to all the other things we've been
우리가했던 모든 다른 것들에 비해 다시 버너에 일
working on I do think the notion of specialists so I didn't talk about that
나는 전문가의 개념은 내가 그것에 대해 얘기하지 않았다고 생각 할 작업
at all but essentially we had a model that was sort of arbitrary image that
기본적으로 모든하지만 우리는 종류의 임의의 이미지를했다 모델을 가지고 그
classification model like JFT which is like seventeen thousand losses or
JFT 같은 분류 모델은 만칠천 손실 또는 같은 인
something it's an internal data that we trained a good general model that could
뭔가는 우리가 할 수있는 좋은 일반 모델을 내부 데이터 훈련있어 그
deal with all those classes and then we found interesting confuse computable
모든 클래스에 대처하고 우리는 흥미로운 혼동이 계산 가능한 발견
classes that are algorithmically like all the kinds of mushrooms in the world
세계에서 버섯의 모든 종류의 같은 알고리즘이다 클래스
and we were trained specialists on data set there were enriched ribbed only
데이터가 풍부한이 유일한 골이 한 세트에 우리는 전문가를 훈련했다
mushroom data primarily and an occasional random images and we could
버섯 주로 데이터와 가끔 임의의 이미지와 우리는 할 수
train fifty such models that reach good at different kinds of things and get
물건의 종류에 좋은 도달 쉰 같은 모델을 훈련받을
pretty significant accuracy increases at the time we we were able to distill it
꽤 상당한 정확도는 우리가 그것을 증류 할 수 있었다 우리시에 증가
into a single model pretty well we haven't really pursued that too much
단일 모델로 꽤 잘 우리가 정말 너무 많은 것을 추구하지 않은
turned out just the mechanics have been training fifty separate models and then
밝혀졌다 그냥 역학 쉰 별도의 모델을 훈련하고있다
distilling them as a bit unwieldy
조금 다루기로 증류
14 exploration and further research has as you say this clearly demonstrates
이 명확하게 보여줍니다 말한대로 14 탐사 및 추가 연구가있다
that we're i mean it's a different objectives were telling the model to do
우리가 걸 내가 그것을 다른 목적이해야 할 모델을 이야기 한 뜻
right we're telling it to use this hard label or use this hard label and also
바로 우리는이 어려운 라벨을 사용하거나이 어려운 라벨을 사용하고 그것을 말하는 거
get this incredibly rich gradient which says like here's a hundred other signals
여기처럼 말한다이 믿을 수 없을만큼 풍부한 그라데이션의 백 다른 신호를 얻을 수
information so in some sense an unfair comparison right you're telling it a lot
정보 어떤 의미에서 불공정 한 비교 바로 당신이 그것을 많이 이야기하고 그래서
more stuff about every example my case so sometimes it's not so much an
내 경우는 그래서 때로는 그렇지 않은 모든 예에 대한 더 많은 물건 너무 많은
operation feeling it's maybe we should be Fig
작업은 어쩌면 우리도해야거야 느낌
figuring out how to feed preacher signals than just a single binary label
단지 하나의 이진 레이블보다 설교자 신호를 공급하는 방법을 알아내는
to our models I think that's probably an interesting area to pursue I we thought
우리의 모델 그게 우리가 생각 나는을 추구하는 아마 흥미있는 영역이라고 생각
about ideas of having a big ensemble of models all training collectively and
모든 훈련 집합 모델의 큰 앙상블을 갖는 아이디어에 대한
sort of exchanging information in the form of their predictions are rather
그 예측의 형태로 정보를 교환의 일종이다 오히려
than in their parameters as I might be much cheaper more network friendly way
해당 매개 변수보다 나는 훨씬 저렴 이상의 네트워크 친화적 인 방법이 될 수 있습니다로
of of collaboratively training on a really big did you train and 1% of the
의의 공동 당신이 훈련의 1 % 않았다 정말 큰에서 훈련
day or something and swap predictions
하루라도 스왑 예측
yeah I mean I think all these kind of radios are worth pursuing the captioning
그래 내가 라디오의 모든 종류의 캡션을 추구하는 가치가있다 생각 의미
workers interesting but it tends to you tend to have many fewer labels with
흥미로운 근로자하지만 당신 경향이 많은 적은 라벨을 갖는 경향이
captions then we have images with sort of hard labels like Jeter Jaguar at
캡션 우리는 지터 재규어 같은 하드 라벨의 종류에 이미지를 가지고
least that are prepared in a clean way I think actually I'm aware there's a lot
깨끗한 방법으로 제조되는 적어도 나는 많은 거기에 내가 알고 있어요 실제로 생각
of images with sentences written about in the trick is identifying which
트릭에 대해 쓴 문장과 이미지로 식별되는
sentences about which image problem some problems you know you don't need to
문장있는 이미지 문제는 당신이 필요하지 않습니다 알고있는 몇 가지 문제에 대한
really train on mine like speech recognition is a good example it's not
정말 음성 인식 등의 광산에 훈련은 그렇지 않은 좋은 예입니다
like human vocal cords change that often the words you say change a little bit so
인간의 성대가 종종 단어를 변경처럼 그렇게 조금 변경 말한다
we redistributions tend to be not very stationary
우리 재배포은 매우 고정하지 경향이있다
like the words everyone collectively says tomorrow are pretty similar to ones
단어 모두가 공동으로 말한다처럼 내일 것과 매우 유사하다
they say today but subtly different like Long Island Chocolate Festival might
그들은 오늘하지만 롱 아일랜드 초콜릿 축제 같은 미묘한 차이가 수도 말
suddenly become more and more prominent over the next two weeks and those kinds
갑자기 더 눈에 띄는 다음 2 주 그 종류 이상이 될
of things you know you need to be cognizant of the fact that you want to
일의 당신은 당신이 원하는 사실을 인식 할 필요가 알고
capture those kinds of effects and one of the ways to do it is to train your
이 양성하는 것입니다 할 그 효과의 종류와 가지 방법 중 하나를 캡처하여
model and a minor sometime he doesn't need to be so online but you like
모델과 작은 언젠가 그는 이렇게 온라인으로 할 필요하지는 않지만 좋아
getting an example and immediately update your model but you know the
예를 받고 즉시 당신의 모델을 업데이트 할 수 있지만 당신은 알고
pentium problem every five minutes or ten minutes or hour or day is sufficient
펜티엄 문제 5 분마다, 10 분 시간 또는 하루에 충분하다
for most problems but it is pretty important to do that for non-stationary
대부분의 문제이지만 것은 아닌 고정을 위해 그렇게 매우 중요
problems like ads or search queries or things that change over time like that
그런 시간이 지남에 따라 변경 광고 나 검색 쿼리 나 물건 같은 문제
right
권리
the third most important I can't say yes
내가 네 말을 할 수없는 세 번째 가장 중요한
yeah I mean noise in training datasets actually happens all the time greats
그래 나는 훈련 데이터 세트에서 잡음이 실제로 모든 시간 유명한 선수를 어떻게 의미
like even if you look at the image that examples occasionally you'll come across
예 때때로 당신이 건너거야 같은 당신은 이미지를 볼 경우에도
one in your life
당신의 인생에서 하나
actually I was just sitting in a meeting with some people who are working on
에서 일하고있는 사실 난 그냥 어떤 사람과의 만남에 앉아 있었다
visualization techniques and one of the things that were visualizing was see far
시각화 기술과 지금까지 볼 수 있었다 시각화 된 것들 중 하나
input data and they had this kind of core presentation of all the C four
입력 데이터들은 모두 C 네 코어 프레젠테이션 이런 있었다
examples all mapped onto like four-by-four pixels each one month on
예는 모두 4 × 4 화소 각각 월에 같은에 매핑
their screen for sixty thousand images and Mike you could kind of pick things
자신의 육만 이미지 화면과 마이크가 가지 일을 선택할 수
out and select them toward and here's one that liked the model predicted with
출력 및 방향을 선택하고 여기에 예측 모델을 좋아 하나
high confidence but it got wrong and it said her plane as the model that
높은 신뢰성하지만 잘못했고, 그것은 말했다 모델로 그녀의 비행기가
airplane and you look at the image and it's an airplane and the label is not
비행기 당신은 이미지를보고는 비행기의 레이블은 아니다
heavily you like I understand why I gotta run so it's you know you want to
주로 내가 실행 야지 왜 당신은 당신이 원하는 알고는 그래서 이해 좋아
make sure your dataset is as clean as possible cuz training and noisy data is
있는지 확인 데이터 집합 교육 사촌 가능한 한 깨끗하고 잡음이 데이터가
generally not as good as
로 일반적으로 좋지 않다
cleaned it out but on the other hand expending too much effort to clean that
그것을 세정하지만 한편 것을 청소 너무 많은 노력을 늘리지
it is often more more effort than its worth to kind of do some filtering kinds
종종 더 많은 종류의 몇 가지 필터링 가지 작업을 수행하는 그 가치보다 더 많은 노력
of things you don't throw out the obvious bad stuff and generally more
일의 당신은 일반적으로 더 명백한 나쁜 물건을 던져하지 않습니다
noisy data is often better than less clean it up
시끄러운 데이터는 최대 그것은 덜 깨끗한보다 종종 더 낫다
depends on the problem but only about one thing to try and then if you're
문제에 따라 달라집니다하지만 당신이 있다면 약 한 것은 다음 시도하고
unhappy with the result then investigate why the question
결과에 만족하지 왜 질문 조사
okay thank you
좋아 감사합니다